[
  [
    {
      "question": "aanvragen",
      "options": [
        "education",
        "to request, to apply for",
        "to give birth",
        "parental contribution"
      ],
      "answer": "to request, to apply for"
    },
    {
      "question": "de aardrijkskunde",
      "options": [
        "geography",
        "family doctor, GP",
        "dependent",
        "subject"
      ],
      "answer": "geography"
    },
    {
      "question": "de advocaat",
      "options": [
        "lawyer",
        "training, education",
        "pre-schooler",
        "at lunchtime"
      ],
      "answer": "lawyer"
    },
    {
      "question": "afhankelijk",
      "options": [
        "dependent",
        "pre-school",
        "after-school care",
        "Islamic"
      ],
      "answer": "dependent"
    },
    {
      "question": "de basisschool",
      "options": [
        "primary/elementary school",
        "adolescent, teenager",
        "maternity assistance",
        "to mistreat"
      ],
      "answer": "primary/elementary school"
    },
    {
      "question": "de begrafenis",
      "options": [
        "funeral",
        "freedom",
        "primary/elementary school",
        "at lunchtime"
      ],
      "answer": "funeral"
    },
    {
      "question": "de belasting",
      "options": [
        "pre-schooler",
        "to tinker, to play",
        "tax(es), tax authorities",
        "subject"
      ],
      "answer": "tax(es), tax authorities"
    },
    {
      "question": "het beroepsonderwijs",
      "options": [
        "pregnant",
        "responsible",
        "vocational/professional training",
        "secondary education"
      ],
      "answer": "vocational/professional training"
    },
    {
      "question": "bevallen",
      "options": [
        "parental contribution",
        "illness, disease",
        "toddlers’ playroom, playgroup",
        "to give birth"
      ],
      "answer": "to give birth"
    },
    {
      "question": "de bevalling",
      "options": [
        "vocational/professional training",
        "birth",
        "respect",
        "higher general secondary education"
      ],
      "answer": "birth"
    },
    {
      "question": "bewegen",
      "options": [
        "gynaecologist",
        "to move",
        "uniform",
        "pre-schooler"
      ],
      "answer": "to move"
    },
    {
      "question": "de bibliotheek",
      "options": [
        "geography",
        "slip, form",
        "Youth Care Agency",
        "library"
      ],
      "answer": "library"
    },
    {
      "question": "de brugklas",
      "options": [
        "organization",
        "first class",
        "to mistreat",
        "respect"
      ],
      "answer": "first class"
    },
    {
      "question": "de buitenschoolse opvang",
      "options": [
        "adolescent, teenager",
        "baby’s book",
        "responsible",
        "out of school care"
      ],
      "answer": "out of school care"
    },
    {
      "question": "Bureau Jeugdzorg",
      "options": [
        "system",
        "Youth Care Agency",
        "education",
        "pre-university education"
      ],
      "answer": "Youth Care Agency"
    },
    {
      "question": "het consultatiebureau",
      "options": [
        "teacher",
        "school guide/prospectus",
        "intermediate vocational education",
        "consultation office, infant welfare centre"
      ],
      "answer": "consultation office, infant welfare centre"
    },
    {
      "question": "het continurooster",
      "options": [
        "system",
        "arithmetic",
        "health insurance",
        "continuous timetable (no breaks between classes)"
      ],
      "answer": "continuous timetable (no breaks between classes)"
    },
    {
      "question": "doorstromen",
      "options": [
        "higher vocational education",
        "health insurance",
        "to count",
        "move up, move on"
      ],
      "answer": "move up, move on"
    },
    {
      "question": "het gastouderbureau",
      "options": [
        "baby-sitting/child care agency",
        "punishment",
        "uniform",
        "after-school care"
      ],
      "answer": "baby-sitting/child care agency"
    },
    {
      "question": "de gelegenheid",
      "options": [
        "opportunity",
        "parents’ night",
        "higher general secondary education",
        "secondary education"
      ],
      "answer": "opportunity"
    },
    {
      "question": "het geloof",
      "options": [
        "continuous timetable (no breaks between classes)",
        "religion",
        "compulsory education",
        "pre-school"
      ],
      "answer": "religion"
    },
    {
      "question": "de geschiedenis",
      "options": [
        "test",
        "baby-sitter",
        "history",
        "obstetrician"
      ],
      "answer": "history"
    },
    {
      "question": "het groeiboekje",
      "options": [
        "higher vocational education",
        "education",
        "baby’s book",
        "age"
      ],
      "answer": "baby’s book"
    },
    {
      "question": "groeien",
      "options": [
        "to grow",
        "to travel without paying a fare",
        "university",
        "secondary education"
      ],
      "answer": "to grow"
    },
    {
      "question": "de gymnastiek",
      "options": [
        "lawyer",
        "history",
        "to enrol, to register",
        "gymnastics"
      ],
      "answer": "gymnastics"
    },
    {
      "question": "de gynaecoloog",
      "options": [
        "secondary education",
        "gynaecologist",
        "obstetrician",
        "break, pause"
      ],
      "answer": "gynaecologist"
    },
    {
      "question": "de handicap",
      "options": [
        "pre-school",
        "handicap, disability",
        "to measure",
        "to mistreat"
      ],
      "answer": "handicap, disability"
    },
    {
      "question": "de handtekening",
      "options": [
        "signature",
        "Social Insurance Bank",
        "to move",
        "to move house, shift"
      ],
      "answer": "signature"
    },
    {
      "question": "de havo",
      "options": [
        "higher general secondary education",
        "to weigh",
        "to read (out aloud) to",
        "age"
      ],
      "answer": "higher general secondary education"
    },
    {
      "question": "het hbo",
      "options": [
        "compulsory",
        "higher vocational education",
        "compulsory education",
        "to study"
      ],
      "answer": "higher vocational education"
    },
    {
      "question": "de huisarts",
      "options": [
        "(child) rearing/raising",
        "family doctor, GP",
        "to draw",
        "punishment"
      ],
      "answer": "family doctor, GP"
    },
    {
      "question": "het inkomen",
      "options": [
        "after-school care",
        "income",
        "parental contribution",
        "baby’s book"
      ],
      "answer": "income"
    },
    {
      "question": "inschrijven",
      "options": [
        "to enrol, to register",
        "library",
        "intermediate vocational education",
        "arithmetic"
      ],
      "answer": "to enrol, to register"
    },
    {
      "question": "islamitisch",
      "options": [
        "Islamic",
        "teacher",
        "to request, to apply for",
        "income"
      ],
      "answer": "Islamic"
    },
    {
      "question": "de juf",
      "options": [
        "first class",
        "library",
        "pre-school",
        "teacher"
      ],
      "answer": "teacher"
    },
    {
      "question": "de kinderbijslag",
      "options": [
        "obstetrician",
        "history",
        "adolescent, teenager",
        "child endowment/benefit"
      ],
      "answer": "child endowment/benefit"
    },
    {
      "question": "het kinderdagverblijf",
      "options": [
        "public school",
        "breakfast",
        "crèche, day care centre",
        "age"
      ],
      "answer": "crèche, day care centre"
    },
    {
      "question": "de kinderopvang",
      "options": [
        "to request, to apply for",
        "child care",
        "child endowment/benefit",
        "baby-sitter"
      ],
      "answer": "child care"
    },
    {
      "question": "de kinderopvangtoeslag",
      "options": [
        "to grow",
        "website",
        "punishment",
        "child care subsidy"
      ],
      "answer": "child care subsidy"
    },
    {
      "question": "de kleuter",
      "options": [
        "pre-schooler",
        "opportunity",
        "Islamic",
        "first class"
      ],
      "answer": "pre-schooler"
    },
    {
      "question": "knutselen",
      "options": [
        "sporting club",
        "vocational/professional training",
        "baby-sitter",
        "to tinker, to play"
      ],
      "answer": "to tinker, to play"
    },
    {
      "question": "de kraamhulp",
      "options": [
        "to grow",
        "maternity assistance",
        "consultation office, infant welfare centre",
        "compulsory"
      ],
      "answer": "maternity assistance"
    },
    {
      "question": "de leeftijd",
      "options": [
        "training, education",
        "organization",
        "to read (out aloud) to",
        "age"
      ],
      "answer": "age"
    },
    {
      "question": "de leerplicht",
      "options": [
        "compulsory education",
        "illness, disease",
        "history",
        "adult"
      ],
      "answer": "compulsory education"
    },
    {
      "question": "het lid",
      "options": [
        "member",
        "age",
        "out of school care",
        "system"
      ],
      "answer": "member"
    },
    {
      "question": "het liedje",
      "options": [
        "training, education",
        "continuous timetable (no breaks between classes)",
        "first class",
        "song"
      ],
      "answer": "song"
    },
    {
      "question": "de mavo",
      "options": [
        "out of school care",
        "compulsory education",
        "secondary education",
        "member"
      ],
      "answer": "secondary education"
    },
    {
      "question": "het mbo",
      "options": [
        "at lunchtime",
        "website",
        "intermediate vocational education",
        "government"
      ],
      "answer": "intermediate vocational education"
    },
    {
      "question": "meten",
      "options": [
        "free choice of school",
        "geography",
        "secondary education",
        "to measure"
      ],
      "answer": "to measure"
    },
    {
      "question": "de middelbare school",
      "options": [
        "to study",
        "lawyer",
        "secondary/high school",
        "respect"
      ],
      "answer": "secondary/high school"
    },
    {
      "question": "mishandelen",
      "options": [
        "website",
        "to mistreat",
        "system",
        "vocational/professional training"
      ],
      "answer": "to mistreat"
    },
    {
      "question": "de naschoolse opvang",
      "options": [
        "secondary education",
        "vaccination",
        "after-school care",
        "sporting club"
      ],
      "answer": "after-school care"
    },
    {
      "question": "het niveau",
      "options": [
        "level",
        "to count",
        "nutrition",
        "to enrol, to register"
      ],
      "answer": "level"
    },
    {
      "question": "het onderwijs",
      "options": [
        "pre-school",
        "education",
        "(child) rearing/raising",
        "parents’ night"
      ],
      "answer": "education"
    },
    {
      "question": "het ontbijt",
      "options": [
        "argument",
        "secondary education",
        "breakfast",
        "education"
      ],
      "answer": "breakfast"
    },
    {
      "question": "de ontwikkeling",
      "options": [
        "development",
        "to read (out aloud) to",
        "to count",
        "pre-university education"
      ],
      "answer": "development"
    },
    {
      "question": "openbaar",
      "options": [
        "secondary education",
        "argument",
        "public",
        "to give birth"
      ],
      "answer": "public"
    },
    {
      "question": "de openbare school",
      "options": [
        "to mistreat",
        "break, pause",
        "to tinker, to play",
        "public school"
      ],
      "answer": "public school"
    },
    {
      "question": "de opleiding",
      "options": [
        "toddlers’ playroom, playgroup",
        "geography",
        "toddler",
        "training, education"
      ],
      "answer": "training, education"
    },
    {
      "question": "de oppas",
      "options": [
        "secondary education",
        "baby-sitting/child care agency",
        "obstetrician",
        "baby-sitter"
      ],
      "answer": "baby-sitter"
    },
    {
      "question": "de opvoeding",
      "options": [
        "(child) rearing/raising",
        "library",
        "gynaecologist",
        "consultation office, infant welfare centre"
      ],
      "answer": "(child) rearing/raising"
    },
    {
      "question": "de organisatie",
      "options": [
        "history",
        "arithmetic",
        "waiting list",
        "organization"
      ],
      "answer": "organization"
    },
    {
      "question": "de ouderavond",
      "options": [
        "parents’ night",
        "higher vocational education",
        "out of school care",
        "child care subsidy"
      ],
      "answer": "parents’ night"
    },
    {
      "question": "de ouderbijdrage",
      "options": [
        "income",
        "to stay at school during lunch break",
        "parental contribution",
        "geography"
      ],
      "answer": "parental contribution"
    },
    {
      "question": "overblijven",
      "options": [
        "age",
        "to draw",
        "to stay at school during lunch break",
        "to move house, shift"
      ],
      "answer": "to stay at school during lunch break"
    },
    {
      "question": "de pauze",
      "options": [
        "secondary education",
        "library",
        "pre-university education",
        "break, pause"
      ],
      "answer": "break, pause"
    },
    {
      "question": "de peuter",
      "options": [
        "toddler",
        "report",
        "to study",
        "Social Insurance Bank"
      ],
      "answer": "toddler"
    },
    {
      "question": "de peuterspeelzaal",
      "options": [
        "vocational/professional training",
        "slip, form",
        "toddlers’ playroom, playgroup",
        "permission"
      ],
      "answer": "toddlers’ playroom, playgroup"
    },
    {
      "question": "de prik",
      "options": [
        "to grow",
        "first class",
        "pre-school",
        "injection, shot"
      ],
      "answer": "injection, shot"
    },
    {
      "question": "de puber",
      "options": [
        "respect",
        "lower secondary professional education",
        "geography",
        "adolescent, teenager"
      ],
      "answer": "adolescent, teenager"
    },
    {
      "question": "het rapport",
      "options": [
        "organization",
        "uniform",
        "report",
        "gymnastics"
      ],
      "answer": "report"
    },
    {
      "question": "de regering",
      "options": [
        "intermediate vocational education",
        "government",
        "Islamic",
        "after-school care"
      ],
      "answer": "government"
    },
    {
      "question": "rekenen",
      "options": [
        "lower secondary professional education",
        "arithmetic",
        "report",
        "family doctor, GP"
      ],
      "answer": "arithmetic"
    },
    {
      "question": "het respect",
      "options": [
        "dependent",
        "vocational/professional training",
        "age",
        "respect"
      ],
      "answer": "respect"
    },
    {
      "question": "de ruzie",
      "options": [
        "pre-schooler",
        "geography",
        "freedom",
        "argument"
      ],
      "answer": "argument"
    },
    {
      "question": "de schoolgids",
      "options": [
        "school guide/prospectus",
        "arithmetic",
        "permission",
        "free choice of school"
      ],
      "answer": "school guide/prospectus"
    },
    {
      "question": "het schoolreisje",
      "options": [
        "to read (out aloud) to",
        "pre-university education",
        "school trip, excursion",
        "geography"
      ],
      "answer": "school trip, excursion"
    },
    {
      "question": "de Sociale Verzekeringsbank",
      "options": [
        "parents’ night",
        "Social Insurance Bank",
        "system",
        "library"
      ],
      "answer": "Social Insurance Bank"
    },
    {
      "question": "de sportclub",
      "options": [
        "funeral",
        "education",
        "sporting club",
        "to travel without paying a fare"
      ],
      "answer": "sporting club"
    },
    {
      "question": "de straf",
      "options": [
        "punishment",
        "tax(es), tax authorities",
        "compulsory education",
        "opportunity"
      ],
      "answer": "punishment"
    },
    {
      "question": "het strookje",
      "options": [
        "public school",
        "slip, form",
        "report",
        "move up, move on"
      ],
      "answer": "slip, form"
    },
    {
      "question": "het systeem",
      "options": [
        "baby’s book",
        "system",
        "responsible",
        "government"
      ],
      "answer": "system"
    },
    {
      "question": "studeren",
      "options": [
        "to study",
        "toddler",
        "gymnastics",
        "public school"
      ],
      "answer": "to study"
    },
    {
      "question": "tekenen",
      "options": [
        "respect",
        "pre-schooler",
        "to draw",
        "adult"
      ],
      "answer": "to draw"
    },
    {
      "question": "tellen",
      "options": [
        "member",
        "song",
        "to count",
        "toddler"
      ],
      "answer": "to count"
    },
    {
      "question": "de test",
      "options": [
        "to grow",
        "pregnant",
        "parental contribution",
        "test"
      ],
      "answer": "test"
    },
    {
      "question": "de toestemming",
      "options": [
        "permission",
        "handicap, disability",
        "member",
        "arithmetic"
      ],
      "answer": "permission"
    },
    {
      "question": "tussen de middag",
      "options": [
        "at lunchtime",
        "organization",
        "adult",
        "report"
      ],
      "answer": "at lunchtime"
    },
    {
      "question": "het uniform",
      "options": [
        "to grow",
        "uniform",
        "out of school care",
        "parents’ night"
      ],
      "answer": "uniform"
    },
    {
      "question": "de universiteit",
      "options": [
        "university",
        "sporting club",
        "(child) rearing/raising",
        "to move"
      ],
      "answer": "university"
    },
    {
      "question": "de vaccinatie",
      "options": [
        "vaccination",
        "freedom",
        "pre-school",
        "child care subsidy"
      ],
      "answer": "vaccination"
    },
    {
      "question": "het vak",
      "options": [
        "primary/elementary school",
        "subject",
        "teacher",
        "lower secondary professional education"
      ],
      "answer": "subject"
    },
    {
      "question": "verantwoordelijk",
      "options": [
        "responsible",
        "history",
        "free choice of school",
        "secondary education"
      ],
      "answer": "responsible"
    },
    {
      "question": "verhuizen",
      "options": [
        "vaccination",
        "teacher",
        "nutrition",
        "to move house, shift"
      ],
      "answer": "to move house, shift"
    },
    {
      "question": "de verloskundige",
      "options": [
        "age",
        "breakfast",
        "obstetrician",
        "pre-schooler"
      ],
      "answer": "obstetrician"
    },
    {
      "question": "verplicht",
      "options": [
        "break, pause",
        "website",
        "compulsory",
        "school guide/prospectus"
      ],
      "answer": "compulsory"
    },
    {
      "question": "het vmbo",
      "options": [
        "lower secondary professional education",
        "compulsory education",
        "test",
        "primary/elementary school"
      ],
      "answer": "lower secondary professional education"
    },
    {
      "question": "de voeding",
      "options": [
        "pregnant",
        "toddler",
        "higher vocational education",
        "nutrition"
      ],
      "answer": "nutrition"
    },
    {
      "question": "volwassen",
      "options": [
        "adult",
        "pre-school",
        "to give birth",
        "to move"
      ],
      "answer": "adult"
    },
    {
      "question": "voorlezen",
      "options": [
        "to tinker, to play",
        "to read (out aloud) to",
        "secondary/high school",
        "toddler"
      ],
      "answer": "to read (out aloud) to"
    },
    {
      "question": "de voorschool",
      "options": [
        "out of school care",
        "consultation office, infant welfare centre",
        "pre-school",
        "organization"
      ],
      "answer": "pre-school"
    },
    {
      "question": "het voortgezet onderwijs",
      "options": [
        "maternity assistance",
        "level",
        "secondary education",
        "permission"
      ],
      "answer": "secondary education"
    },
    {
      "question": "de vrijheid",
      "options": [
        "respect",
        "to move house, shift",
        "report",
        "freedom"
      ],
      "answer": "freedom"
    },
    {
      "question": "de vrijheid van onderwijs",
      "options": [
        "free choice of school",
        "baby-sitter",
        "training, education",
        "Youth Care Agency"
      ],
      "answer": "free choice of school"
    },
    {
      "question": "het vwo",
      "options": [
        "pre-university education",
        "geography",
        "system",
        "secondary education"
      ],
      "answer": "pre-university education"
    },
    {
      "question": "de wachtlijst",
      "options": [
        "geography",
        "child care subsidy",
        "waiting list",
        "to weigh"
      ],
      "answer": "waiting list"
    },
    {
      "question": "de website",
      "options": [
        "age",
        "handicap, disability",
        "website",
        "higher vocational education"
      ],
      "answer": "website"
    },
    {
      "question": "wegen",
      "options": [
        "to count",
        "uniform",
        "to weigh",
        "dependent"
      ],
      "answer": "to weigh"
    },
    {
      "question": "de ziekte",
      "options": [
        "Islamic",
        "to move house, shift",
        "illness, disease",
        "break, pause"
      ],
      "answer": "illness, disease"
    },
    {
      "question": "de zorgverzekering",
      "options": [
        "health insurance",
        "school trip, excursion",
        "income",
        "to count"
      ],
      "answer": "health insurance"
    },
    {
      "question": "zwanger",
      "options": [
        "to weigh",
        "to mistreat",
        "pregnant",
        "at lunchtime"
      ],
      "answer": "pregnant"
    },
    {
      "question": "zwart reizen",
      "options": [
        "illness, disease",
        "teacher",
        "to travel without paying a fare",
        "pre-schooler"
      ],
      "answer": "to travel without paying a fare"
    }
  ],
  {
    "question": "de dief?",
    "options": [
      "online banking",
      "youth affairs, child welfare",
      "thief",
      "fine"
    ],
    "answer": "thief"
  },
  {
    "question": "het tekort?",
    "options": [
      "proof of having reported to the police",
      "health costs/expenses",
      "negative balance",
      "code"
    ],
    "answer": "negative balance"
  },
  {
    "question": "het rekeningnummer?",
    "options": [
      "judge, magistrate",
      "level",
      "bank account number",
      "insurance"
    ],
    "answer": "bank account number"
  },
  {
    "question": "de huurtoeslag?",
    "options": [
      "social counsellors",
      "(for) an indefinite period of time",
      "signature",
      "rent subsidy/benefit"
    ],
    "answer": "rent subsidy/benefit"
  },
  {
    "question": "het openbaar vervoer?",
    "options": [
      "aliens registration office, aliens police",
      "bank account",
      "public transportation",
      "right"
    ],
    "answer": "public transportation"
  },
  {
    "question": "de verblijfsvergunning?",
    "options": [
      "negative balance",
      "legal aid office",
      "right",
      "residence permit"
    ],
    "answer": "residence permit"
  },
  {
    "question": "de belasting?",
    "options": [
      "tax(es), tax authorities",
      "portfolio",
      "municipality, city, local council",
      "possible"
    ],
    "answer": "tax(es), tax authorities"
  },
  {
    "question": "de vrijstelling?",
    "options": [
      "signature",
      "(hospital) admission, hospitalization",
      "therapy",
      "exemption"
    ],
    "answer": "exemption"
  },
  {
    "question": "intoetsen?",
    "options": [
      "reminder",
      "knowledge of Dutch society",
      "objection, complaint",
      "to enter"
    ],
    "answer": "to enter"
  },
  {
    "question": "het basisexamen inburgering?",
    "options": [
      "(for) an indefinite period of time",
      "police station",
      "to request, to apply for",
      "civic integration examination A1 abroad"
    ],
    "answer": "civic integration examination A1 abroad"
  },
  {
    "question": "het portfolio?",
    "options": [
      "knowledge of Dutch society",
      "lawsuit, (legal) case",
      "portfolio",
      "subsidy, benefit"
    ],
    "answer": "portfolio"
  },
  {
    "question": "de rekening?",
    "options": [
      "bill",
      "code",
      "exemption",
      "reminder"
    ],
    "answer": "bill"
  },
  {
    "question": "verplicht?",
    "options": [
      "naturalization exam",
      "to vote",
      "compulsory, obligatory",
      "legal"
    ],
    "answer": "compulsory, obligatory"
  },
  {
    "question": "de naturalisatie?",
    "options": [
      "youth affairs, child welfare",
      "naturalization",
      "cashomat, (cash) dispenser",
      "identity card, identification"
    ],
    "answer": "naturalization"
  },
  {
    "question": "het visum?",
    "options": [
      "visa",
      "child endowment",
      "obligation of naturalization",
      "conductor, ticket collector"
    ],
    "answer": "visa"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sociaal Raadslieden?",
    "options": [
      "amount",
      "social counsellors",
      "legal aid office",
      "to open"
    ],
    "answer": "social counsellors"
  },
  {
    "question": "het paspoort?",
    "options": [
      "passport",
      "to refer",
      "bilanço",
      "naturalization"
    ],
    "answer": "passport"
  },
  {
    "question": "de gemeente?",
    "options": [
      "bilanço",
      "conductor, ticket collector",
      "noise",
      "municipality, city, local council"
    ],
    "answer": "municipality, city, local council"
  },
  {
    "question": "contant?",
    "options": [
      "purse, wallet",
      "diploma, degree",
      "lawyer",
      "cash"
    ],
    "answer": "cash"
  },
  {
    "question": "de Sociale Verzekeringsbank?",
    "options": [
      "direct debit",
      "bilanço",
      "Social Insurance Bank",
      "level"
    ],
    "answer": "Social Insurance Bank"
  },
  {
    "question": "het Bureau voor Rechtshulp?",
    "options": [
      "legal aid office",
      "judge, magistrate",
      "rent",
      "to open"
    ],
    "answer": "legal aid office"
  },
  {
    "question": "het geweld?",
    "options": [
      "negative",
      "digital account for government services",
      "website",
      "violence"
    ],
    "answer": "violence"
  },
  {
    "question": "het wachtwoord?",
    "options": [
      "visa",
      "password",
      "fine",
      "portfolio"
    ],
    "answer": "password"
  },
  {
    "question": "het sofinummer?",
    "options": [
      "(pre-printed) payment slip",
      "National Insurance Number, Social Security Number",
      "reminder",
      "password"
    ],
    "answer": "National Insurance Number, Social Security Number"
  },
  {
    "question": "de incasso?",
    "options": [
      "public transportation",
      "provision of (government) services",
      "direct debit",
      "instalment regular interval"
    ],
    "answer": "direct debit"
  },
  {
    "question": "de BTW?",
    "options": [
      "VAT – Value Added Tax",
      "obligation of naturalization",
      "policeman",
      "police station"
    ],
    "answer": "VAT – Value Added Tax"
  },
  {
    "question": "inburgeringsplicht?",
    "options": [
      "obligation of naturalization",
      "Dutch job market orientation",
      "to transfer (money)",
      "the social work"
    ],
    "answer": "obligation of naturalization"
  },
  {
    "question": "de kinderopvang?",
    "options": [
      "crèche, day care centre",
      "garage",
      "request, application",
      "signature"
    ],
    "answer": "crèche, day care centre"
  },
  {
    "question": "het bezwaar?",
    "options": [
      "proof of having reported to the police",
      "objection, complaint",
      "to be troubled/annoyed by",
      "to protest"
    ],
    "answer": "objection, complaint"
  },
  {
    "question": "het medicijn?",
    "options": [
      "judge, magistrate",
      "emergency number",
      "medicine",
      "nationality"
    ],
    "answer": "medicine"
  },
  {
    "question": "behandelen?",
    "options": [
      "family doctor, GP",
      "the social work",
      "to treat, to deal with",
      "Social Insurance Bank"
    ],
    "answer": "to treat, to deal with"
  },
  {
    "question": "de nieuwkomer?",
    "options": [
      "Dutch job market orientation",
      "conversation",
      "newcomer, new arrival",
      "child budget"
    ],
    "answer": "newcomer, new arrival"
  },
  {
    "question": "ONA – Oriëntatie op de Nederlandse Arbeidsmarkt?",
    "options": [
      "PIN code",
      "asylum seeker, refugee",
      "document",
      "Dutch job market orientation"
    ],
    "answer": "Dutch job market orientation"
  },
  {
    "question": "de maatschappelijk werker?",
    "options": [
      "social worker",
      "policeman",
      "youth affairs, child welfare",
      "naturalization exam"
    ],
    "answer": "social worker"
  },
  {
    "question": "het juridisch loket?",
    "options": [
      "lawyer",
      "legal counter/desk",
      "noise",
      "purse, wallet"
    ],
    "answer": "legal counter/desk"
  },
  {
    "question": "de heffingskorting?",
    "options": [
      "to travel",
      "document",
      "tax rebate",
      "medicine"
    ],
    "answer": "tax rebate"
  },
  {
    "question": "de kinderbijslag?",
    "options": [
      "conductor, ticket collector",
      "tax rebate",
      "child endowment",
      "(hospital) admission, hospitalization"
    ],
    "answer": "child endowment"
  },
  {
    "question": "de pasfoto?",
    "options": [
      "identity card, identification",
      "passport photo",
      "code",
      "to move house"
    ],
    "answer": "passport photo"
  },
  {
    "question": "de toeslag?",
    "options": [
      "officialy",
      "subsidy, benefit",
      "government",
      "level"
    ],
    "answer": "subsidy, benefit"
  },
  {
    "question": "protesteren?",
    "options": [
      "to transfer (money)",
      "Youth Care Agency",
      "provision of (government) services",
      "to protest"
    ],
    "answer": "to protest"
  },
  {
    "question": "de portemonnee?",
    "options": [
      "National Insurance Number, Social Security Number",
      "fine",
      "purse, wallet",
      "violence"
    ],
    "answer": "purse, wallet"
  },
  {
    "question": "stemmen?",
    "options": [
      "tax authorities",
      "to vote",
      "to inform",
      "health allowance"
    ],
    "answer": "to vote"
  },
  {
    "question": "de geldautomaat?",
    "options": [
      "ATM",
      "government language exam",
      "obligation of naturalization",
      "amount"
    ],
    "answer": "ATM"
  },
  {
    "question": "het kinderdagverblijf?",
    "options": [
      "to treat, to deal with",
      "officialy",
      "judge, magistrate",
      "youth affairs, child welfare"
    ],
    "answer": "youth affairs, child welfare"
  },
  {
    "question": "het inburgeringsexamen?",
    "options": [
      "government language exam",
      "request, application",
      "to enter a pin code, pay by switch card",
      "naturalization exam"
    ],
    "answer": "naturalization exam"
  },
  {
    "question": "regulier?",
    "options": [
      "normal, regular",
      "to move house",
      "obligation of naturalization",
      "residence permit"
    ],
    "answer": "normal, regular"
  },
  {
    "question": "de automaat?",
    "options": [
      "cashomat, (cash) dispenser",
      "National Insurance Number, Social Security Number",
      "violence",
      "newcomer, new arrival"
    ],
    "answer": "cashomat, (cash) dispenser"
  },
  {
    "question": "overmaken?",
    "options": [
      "to transfer (money)",
      "to refer",
      "permit, license",
      "bank account number"
    ],
    "answer": "to transfer (money)"
  },
  {
    "question": "de klacht?",
    "options": [
      "complaint",
      "amount",
      "legal",
      "newcomer, new arrival"
    ],
    "answer": "complaint"
  },
  {
    "question": "de advocaat?",
    "options": [
      "portfolio",
      "request, application",
      "lawyer",
      "drivers license"
    ],
    "answer": "lawyer"
  },
  {
    "question": "de huisarts?",
    "options": [
      "family doctor, GP",
      "online banking",
      "ATM",
      "exemption, being let off having to pay"
    ],
    "answer": "family doctor, GP"
  },
  {
    "question": "de opname?",
    "options": [
      "social counsellors",
      "bank account number",
      "(hospital) admission, hospitalization",
      "permission"
    ],
    "answer": "(hospital) admission, hospitalization"
  },
  {
    "question": "het verpleeghuis?",
    "options": [
      "old arrival",
      "nursing home",
      "bank statement",
      "therapy"
    ],
    "answer": "nursing home"
  },
  {
    "question": "de immigratie?",
    "options": [
      "nursing home",
      "medicine",
      "immigration",
      "the social work"
    ],
    "answer": "immigration"
  },
  {
    "question": "de ruzie?",
    "options": [
      "conversation",
      "lawyer",
      "digital account for government services",
      "argument"
    ],
    "answer": "argument"
  },
  {
    "question": "het niveau?",
    "options": [
      "level",
      "garage",
      "(pre-printed) payment slip",
      "to transfer (money)"
    ],
    "answer": "level"
  },
  {
    "question": "het lawaai?",
    "options": [
      "aliens registration office, aliens police",
      "noise",
      "to inform",
      "argument"
    ],
    "answer": "noise"
  },
  {
    "question": "het staatsexamen NT2?",
    "options": [
      "emergency number",
      "tax rebate",
      "child budget",
      "government language exam"
    ],
    "answer": "government language exam"
  },
  {
    "question": "de oudkomer?",
    "options": [
      "National Insurance Number, Social Security Number",
      "old arrival",
      "home care",
      "social worker"
    ],
    "answer": "old arrival"
  },
  {
    "question": "doorgeven?",
    "options": [
      "visa",
      "negative balance",
      "to inform",
      "treatment"
    ],
    "answer": "to inform"
  },
  {
    "question": "de ziektekosten?",
    "options": [
      "tax authorities",
      "to report something (to the police); to submit a statement of income to the tax office",
      "health costs/expenses",
      "to enter"
    ],
    "answer": "health costs/expenses"
  },
  {
    "question": "het ongeluk?",
    "options": [
      "noise",
      "bank statement",
      "accident",
      "visa"
    ],
    "answer": "accident"
  },
  {
    "question": "de identiteitskaart?",
    "options": [
      "to open",
      "identity card",
      "municipality, city, local council",
      "child endowment"
    ],
    "answer": "identity card"
  },
  {
    "question": "mogelijk?",
    "options": [
      "possible",
      "health costs/expenses",
      "cash",
      "automatically"
    ],
    "answer": "possible"
  },
  {
    "question": "doorverwijzen?",
    "options": [
      "judge, magistrate",
      "to refer",
      "password",
      "the social work"
    ],
    "answer": "to refer"
  },
  {
    "question": "de machtiging?",
    "options": [
      "authorization, standing order",
      "document",
      "depression",
      "Social Insurance Bank"
    ],
    "answer": "authorization, standing order"
  },
  {
    "question": "de vergunning?",
    "options": [
      "to block (a bank account)",
      "newcomer, new arrival",
      "permit, license",
      "to request, to apply for"
    ],
    "answer": "permit, license"
  },
  {
    "question": "asiel?",
    "options": [
      "signature",
      "asylum",
      "purse, wallet",
      "to inform"
    ],
    "answer": "asylum"
  },
  {
    "question": "de garage?",
    "options": [
      "newcomer, new arrival",
      "garage",
      "judge, magistrate",
      "residence permit"
    ],
    "answer": "garage"
  },
  {
    "question": "het inkomen?",
    "options": [
      "to naturalize",
      "drivers license",
      "tax(es), tax authorities",
      "income"
    ],
    "answer": "income"
  },
  {
    "question": "de rechtszaak?",
    "options": [
      "bank account",
      "instalment regular interval",
      "lawsuit, (legal) case",
      "insurance"
    ],
    "answer": "lawsuit, (legal) case"
  },
  {
    "question": "het maatschappelijk werk?",
    "options": [
      "the social work",
      "to enter a pin code, pay by switch card",
      "naturalization exam",
      "medicine"
    ],
    "answer": "the social work"
  },
  {
    "question": "de therapie?",
    "options": [
      "treatment",
      "exemption",
      "therapy",
      "family doctor, GP"
    ],
    "answer": "therapy"
  },
  {
    "question": "verlengen?",
    "options": [
      "newcomer, new arrival",
      "noise",
      "proof of having reported to the police",
      "to extend, to renew"
    ],
    "answer": "to extend, to renew"
  },
  {
    "question": "de nationaliteit?",
    "options": [
      "nationality",
      "residence permit",
      "to pass (an exam)",
      "asylum seeker, refugee"
    ],
    "answer": "nationality"
  },
  {
    "question": "het internetbankieren?",
    "options": [
      "online banking",
      "to vote",
      "birth extract, proof of identity and/or residence",
      "Dutch job market orientation"
    ],
    "answer": "online banking"
  },
  {
    "question": "rood staan?",
    "options": [
      "old arrival",
      "fine",
      "Dutch job market orientation",
      "overdraft(ing your bank account)"
    ],
    "answer": "overdraft(ing your bank account)"
  },
  {
    "question": "verdienen?",
    "options": [
      "to pass (an exam)",
      "to protest",
      "authorization, standing order",
      "to earn"
    ],
    "answer": "to earn"
  },
  {
    "question": "gelijk hebben?",
    "options": [
      "bank statement",
      "code",
      "bank account number",
      "to be right"
    ],
    "answer": "to be right"
  },
  {
    "question": "aanvragen?",
    "options": [
      "to request, to apply for",
      "bank statement",
      "police station",
      "noise"
    ],
    "answer": "to request, to apply for"
  },
  {
    "question": "het bewijs van aangifte?",
    "options": [
      "to move house",
      "proof of having reported to the police",
      "social worker",
      "to threaten"
    ],
    "answer": "proof of having reported to the police"
  },
  {
    "question": "de behandeling?",
    "options": [
      "to refer",
      "to solve",
      "violence",
      "treatment"
    ],
    "answer": "treatment"
  },
  {
    "question": "het identiteitsbewijs?",
    "options": [
      "to divorce (your husband or wife)",
      "Youth Care Agency",
      "identity card, identification",
      "objection, complaint"
    ],
    "answer": "identity card, identification"
  },
  {
    "question": "het burgerservicenummer (bsn)?",
    "options": [
      "National Insurance Number, Social Security Number",
      "PIN code",
      "child endowment",
      "insurance"
    ],
    "answer": "National Insurance Number, Social Security Number"
  },
  {
    "question": "de kinderopvangtoeslag?",
    "options": [
      "normal, regular",
      "automatically",
      "(for) an indefinite period of time",
      "child care subsidy"
    ],
    "answer": "child care subsidy"
  },
  {
    "question": "de huur?",
    "options": [
      "visa",
      "social worker",
      "rent",
      "instalment regular interval"
    ],
    "answer": "rent"
  },
  {
    "question": "last hebben van?",
    "options": [
      "to be troubled/annoyed by",
      "to vote",
      "birth extract, proof of identity and/or residence",
      "National Insurance Number, Social Security Number"
    ],
    "answer": "to be troubled/annoyed by"
  },
  {
    "question": "de asielzoeker?",
    "options": [
      "compulsory, obligatory",
      "legal aid office",
      "asylum seeker, refugee",
      "treatment"
    ],
    "answer": "asylum seeker, refugee"
  },
  {
    "question": "negatief?",
    "options": [
      "negative",
      "PIN code",
      "to extend, to renew",
      "amount"
    ],
    "answer": "negative"
  },
  {
    "question": "het huishouden?",
    "options": [
      "visa",
      "child care subsidy",
      "housekeeping, household chores",
      "Dutch job market orientation"
    ],
    "answer": "housekeeping, household chores"
  },
  {
    "question": "verhuizen?",
    "options": [
      "child endowment",
      "to move house",
      "purse, wallet",
      "portfolio"
    ],
    "answer": "to move house"
  },
  {
    "question": "het bedrag?",
    "options": [
      "insurance",
      "amount",
      "asylum seeker, refugee",
      "civic integration examination A1 abroad"
    ],
    "answer": "amount"
  },
  {
    "question": "de verzekering?",
    "options": [
      "exemption",
      "insurance",
      "nursing home",
      "civic integration examination A1 abroad"
    ],
    "answer": "insurance"
  },
  {
    "question": "het diploma?",
    "options": [
      "diploma, degree",
      "to vote",
      "online banking",
      "civic integration examination A1 abroad"
    ],
    "answer": "diploma, degree"
  },
  {
    "question": "de aangifte doen?",
    "options": [
      "to report something (to the police); to submit a statement of income to the tax office",
      "naturalization exam",
      "asylum seeker, refugee",
      "online banking"
    ],
    "answer": "to report something (to the police); to submit a statement of income to the tax office"
  },
  {
    "question": "de pincode?",
    "options": [
      "PIN code",
      "child care subsidy",
      "National Insurance Number, Social Security Number",
      "level"
    ],
    "answer": "PIN code"
  },
  {
    "question": "de termijn?",
    "options": [
      "negative balance",
      "instalment regular interval",
      "PIN code",
      "government"
    ],
    "answer": "instalment regular interval"
  },
  {
    "question": "Bureau Jeugdzorg?",
    "options": [
      "income",
      "bill",
      "health allowance",
      "Youth Care Agency"
    ],
    "answer": "Youth Care Agency"
  },
  {
    "question": "het alarmnummer?",
    "options": [
      "lawsuit, (legal) case",
      "violence",
      "to enter a pin code, pay by switch card",
      "emergency number"
    ],
    "answer": "emergency number"
  },
  {
    "question": "pinnen?",
    "options": [
      "legal counter/desk",
      "lawyer",
      "residence permit",
      "to enter a pin code, pay by switch card"
    ],
    "answer": "to enter a pin code, pay by switch card"
  },
  {
    "question": "het kindgebonden budget?",
    "options": [
      "digital account for government services",
      "pass",
      "child budget",
      "to request, to apply for"
    ],
    "answer": "child budget"
  },
  {
    "question": "de handtekening?",
    "options": [
      "argument",
      "overdraft(ing your bank account)",
      "signature",
      "to protest"
    ],
    "answer": "signature"
  },
  {
    "question": "officieel?",
    "options": [
      "asylum seeker, refugee",
      "officialy",
      "proof of having reported to the police",
      "income"
    ],
    "answer": "officialy"
  },
  {
    "question": "het gesprek?",
    "options": [
      "conversation",
      "accident",
      "nursing home",
      "to be troubled/annoyed by"
    ],
    "answer": "conversation"
  },
  {
    "question": "het rijbewijs?",
    "options": [
      "permit, license",
      "drivers license",
      "judge, magistrate",
      "municipality, city, local council"
    ],
    "answer": "drivers license"
  },
  {
    "question": "de kwijtschelding?",
    "options": [
      "treatment",
      "provision of (government) services",
      "tax authorities",
      "exemption, being let off having to pay"
    ],
    "answer": "exemption, being let off having to pay"
  },
  {
    "question": "de regering?",
    "options": [
      "to be troubled/annoyed by",
      "government",
      "instalment regular interval",
      "to pass (an exam)"
    ],
    "answer": "government"
  },
  {
    "question": "de rechter?",
    "options": [
      "Social Insurance Bank",
      "policeman",
      "judge, magistrate",
      "garage"
    ],
    "answer": "judge, magistrate"
  },
  {
    "question": "het saldo?",
    "options": [
      "bilanço",
      "Dutch job market orientation",
      "to solve",
      "to vote"
    ],
    "answer": "bilanço"
  },
  {
    "question": "de pas, het pasje?",
    "options": [
      "pass",
      "right",
      "residence permit",
      "immigration"
    ],
    "answer": "pass"
  },
  {
    "question": "scheiden?",
    "options": [
      "to divorce (your husband or wife)",
      "cashomat, (cash) dispenser",
      "password",
      "government"
    ],
    "answer": "to divorce (your husband or wife)"
  },
  {
    "question": "de zorgtoeslag?",
    "options": [
      "exemption",
      "instalment regular interval",
      "health allowance",
      "drivers license"
    ],
    "answer": "health allowance"
  },
  {
    "question": "(voor) onbepaalde tijd?",
    "options": [
      "identity card, identification",
      "passport",
      "social worker",
      "(for) an indefinite period of time"
    ],
    "answer": "(for) an indefinite period of time"
  },
  {
    "question": "bedreigen?",
    "options": [
      "conversation",
      "negative balance",
      "to threaten",
      "subsidy, benefit"
    ],
    "answer": "to threaten"
  },
  {
    "question": "de bankrekening?",
    "options": [
      "password",
      "complaint",
      "bank account",
      "negative balance"
    ],
    "answer": "bank account"
  },
  {
    "question": "de politieagent?",
    "options": [
      "identity card, identification",
      "to divorce (your husband or wife)",
      "policeman",
      "nationality"
    ],
    "answer": "policeman"
  },
  {
    "question": "de bekeuring?",
    "options": [
      "knowledge of Dutch society",
      "negative",
      "fine",
      "child care subsidy"
    ],
    "answer": "fine"
  },
  {
    "question": "inburgeren?",
    "options": [
      "to divorce (your husband or wife)",
      "to naturalize",
      "National Insurance Number, Social Security Number",
      "to extend, to renew"
    ],
    "answer": "to naturalize"
  },
  {
    "question": "KNS – Kennis van de Nederlandse Samenleving?",
    "options": [
      "bank statement",
      "knowledge of Dutch society",
      "password",
      "level"
    ],
    "answer": "knowledge of Dutch society"
  },
  {
    "question": "het recht?",
    "options": [
      "right",
      "compulsory, obligatory",
      "to be troubled/annoyed by",
      "digital account for government services"
    ],
    "answer": "right"
  },
  {
    "question": "de vreemdelingenpolitie?",
    "options": [
      "aliens registration office, aliens police",
      "compulsory, obligatory",
      "to earn",
      "Youth Care Agency"
    ],
    "answer": "aliens registration office, aliens police"
  },
  {
    "question": "blokkeren?",
    "options": [
      "old arrival",
      "automatically",
      "accident",
      "to block (a bank account)"
    ],
    "answer": "to block (a bank account)"
  },
  {
    "question": "het document?",
    "options": [
      "accident",
      "government language exam",
      "document",
      "ATM"
    ],
    "answer": "document"
  },
  {
    "question": "reizen?",
    "options": [
      "exemption",
      "to travel",
      "rent subsidy/benefit",
      "direct debit"
    ],
    "answer": "to travel"
  },
  {
    "question": "het bankafschrift?",
    "options": [
      "right",
      "bank statement",
      "complaint",
      "negative balance"
    ],
    "answer": "bank statement"
  },
  {
    "question": "de thuiszorg?",
    "options": [
      "home care",
      "tax rebate",
      "cashomat, (cash) dispenser",
      "child endowment"
    ],
    "answer": "home care"
  },
  {
    "question": "de website?",
    "options": [
      "website",
      "asylum seeker, refugee",
      "treatment",
      "birth extract, proof of identity and/or residence"
    ],
    "answer": "website"
  },
  {
    "question": "oplossen?",
    "options": [
      "to naturalize",
      "to solve",
      "complaint",
      "to enter"
    ],
    "answer": "to solve"
  },
  {
    "question": "de instantie?",
    "options": [
      "authority, government agency",
      "amount",
      "policeman",
      "obligation of naturalization"
    ],
    "answer": "authority, government agency"
  },
  {
    "question": "KNM – Kennis van de Nederlandse Maatschappij?",
    "options": [
      "knowledge of Dutch society",
      "asylum seeker, refugee",
      "website",
      "(pre-printed) payment slip"
    ],
    "answer": "knowledge of Dutch society"
  },
  {
    "question": "het politiebureau?",
    "options": [
      "family doctor, GP",
      "valid",
      "garage",
      "police station"
    ],
    "answer": "police station"
  },
  {
    "question": "(voor) bepaalde tijd?",
    "options": [
      "naturalization",
      "child care subsidy",
      "compulsory, obligatory",
      "(for) a specific period of time"
    ],
    "answer": "(for) a specific period of time"
  },
  {
    "question": "de herinnering?",
    "options": [
      "purse, wallet",
      "to move house",
      "objection, complaint",
      "reminder"
    ],
    "answer": "reminder"
  },
  {
    "question": "slagen?",
    "options": [
      "signature",
      "asylum",
      "permission",
      "to pass (an exam)"
    ],
    "answer": "to pass (an exam)"
  },
  {
    "question": "het uittreksel (uit de gemeentelijke basisadministratie)?",
    "options": [
      "birth extract, proof of identity and/or residence",
      "bill",
      "crèche, day care centre",
      "Dutch job market orientation"
    ],
    "answer": "birth extract, proof of identity and/or residence"
  },
  {
    "question": "de dienstverlening?",
    "options": [
      "bank statement",
      "bilanço",
      "provision of (government) services",
      "to be troubled/annoyed by"
    ],
    "answer": "provision of (government) services"
  },
  {
    "question": "de depressie?",
    "options": [
      "to earn",
      "government language exam",
      "depression",
      "pass"
    ],
    "answer": "depression"
  },
  {
    "question": "juridisch?",
    "options": [
      "to report something (to the police); to submit a statement of income to the tax office",
      "legal",
      "civic integration examination A1 abroad",
      "passport photo"
    ],
    "answer": "legal"
  },
  {
    "question": "geldig?",
    "options": [
      "possible",
      "valid",
      "National Insurance Number, Social Security Number",
      "authorization, standing order"
    ],
    "answer": "valid"
  },
  {
    "question": "de conducteur?",
    "options": [
      "to be right",
      "insurance",
      "conductor, ticket collector",
      "normal, regular"
    ],
    "answer": "conductor, ticket collector"
  },
  {
    "question": "de code?",
    "options": [
      "residence permit",
      "direct debit",
      "code",
      "to divorce (your husband or wife)"
    ],
    "answer": "code"
  },
  {
    "question": "het gemeentehuis?",
    "options": [
      "drivers license",
      "housekeeping, household chores",
      "town hall",
      "argument"
    ],
    "answer": "town hall"
  },
  {
    "question": "de Belastingdienst?",
    "options": [
      "tax authorities",
      "bank statement",
      "pass",
      "passport"
    ],
    "answer": "tax authorities"
  },
  {
    "question": "openen?",
    "options": [
      "objection, complaint",
      "pass",
      "to open",
      "drivers license"
    ],
    "answer": "to open"
  },
  {
    "question": "de acceptgiro?",
    "options": [
      "(pre-printed) payment slip",
      "level",
      "obligation of naturalization",
      "lawyer"
    ],
    "answer": "(pre-printed) payment slip"
  },
  {
    "question": "de toestemming?",
    "options": [
      "child care subsidy",
      "income",
      "permission",
      "cash"
    ],
    "answer": "permission"
  },
  {
    "question": "automatisch?",
    "options": [
      "website",
      "police station",
      "automatically",
      "violence"
    ],
    "answer": "automatically"
  },
  {
    "question": "de DigiD?",
    "options": [
      "provision of (government) services",
      "digital account for government services",
      "tax rebate",
      "identity card"
    ],
    "answer": "digital account for government services"
  },
  {
    "question": "de aanvraag?",
    "options": [
      "passport photo",
      "conductor, ticket collector",
      "request, application",
      "amount"
    ],
    "answer": "request, application"
  },
  {
    "question": "aanbieden (aangeboden)",
    "options": [
      "to offer",
      "electricity/gas/utility/power company",
      "gas meter",
      "customer, client"
    ],
    "answer": "to offer"
  },
  {
    "question": "de aansprakelijkheidsverzekering",
    "options": [
      "district",
      "home contents",
      "dependent",
      "(personal) liability insurance/third-party insurance"
    ],
    "answer": "(personal) liability insurance/third-party insurance"
  },
  {
    "question": "aanvragen",
    "options": [
      "window pane",
      "compulsory, obligatory",
      "to request, to apply for",
      "single-family dwelling"
    ],
    "answer": "to request, to apply for"
  },
  {
    "question": "het abonnement",
    "options": [
      "real estate agent",
      "subscription",
      "rubbish disposal charge",
      "glass recycling bin"
    ],
    "answer": "subscription"
  },
  {
    "question": "de advertentie",
    "options": [
      "(classified) advertisement",
      "annual bill",
      "possible",
      "to smell"
    ],
    "answer": "(classified) advertisement"
  },
  {
    "question": "afhankelijk",
    "options": [
      "glass recycling bin",
      "dependent",
      "gas",
      "lift, elevator"
    ],
    "answer": "dependent"
  },
  {
    "question": "afsluiten (van gas en elektriciteit)",
    "options": [
      "compulsory, obligatory",
      "to disconnect, to cut off",
      "annual bill",
      "vehicle insurance"
    ],
    "answer": "to disconnect, to cut off"
  },
  {
    "question": "het afval",
    "options": [
      "rubbish, trash, garbage",
      "website",
      "glass recycling bin",
      "property tax/rates"
    ],
    "answer": "rubbish, trash, garbage"
  },
  {
    "question": "afval scheiden",
    "options": [
      "(classified) advertisement",
      "to separate waste",
      "to order",
      "apartment"
    ],
    "answer": "to separate waste"
  },
  {
    "question": "de afvalstoffenheffing",
    "options": [
      "rubbish disposal charge",
      "window pane",
      "vehicle insurance",
      "repair(s)"
    ],
    "answer": "rubbish disposal charge"
  },
  {
    "question": "het apparaat",
    "options": [
      "housing permit",
      "(electrical) appliance",
      "washing machine",
      "rubbish"
    ],
    "answer": "(electrical) appliance"
  },
  {
    "question": "het appartement",
    "options": [
      "(insurance) policy",
      "property tax/rates",
      "apartment",
      "to rent"
    ],
    "answer": "apartment"
  },
  {
    "question": "de autoverzekering",
    "options": [
      "fire",
      "vehicle insurance",
      "certificate of urgency/need",
      "A label"
    ],
    "answer": "vehicle insurance"
  },
  {
    "question": "de avp",
    "options": [
      "housing corporation",
      "environment",
      "the liability insurance for private persons",
      "student"
    ],
    "answer": "the liability insurance for private persons"
  },
  {
    "question": "de bal",
    "options": [
      "window pane",
      "home insurance",
      "ball",
      "property tax/rates"
    ],
    "answer": "ball"
  },
  {
    "question": "de basisverzekering",
    "options": [
      "nursing home",
      "basic healthcare insurance",
      "storm",
      "health"
    ],
    "answer": "basic healthcare insurance"
  },
  {
    "question": "de batterij",
    "options": [
      "home insurance",
      "income",
      "to offer",
      "battery"
    ],
    "answer": "battery"
  },
  {
    "question": "het bedrag",
    "options": [
      "to sign",
      "to repair, to fix",
      "amount",
      "tax(es)"
    ],
    "answer": "amount"
  },
  {
    "question": "het bedrijf",
    "options": [
      "firm, concern, company",
      "chemical waste",
      "housing association",
      "space, room"
    ],
    "answer": "firm, concern, company"
  },
  {
    "question": "de bekeuring",
    "options": [
      "health insurance",
      "fine",
      "lessor, landlord",
      "to respond"
    ],
    "answer": "fine"
  },
  {
    "question": "de belasting",
    "options": [
      "maintenance",
      "rubbish disposal charge",
      "tax(es)",
      "compulsory, obligatory"
    ],
    "answer": "tax(es)"
  },
  {
    "question": "de Belastingdienst",
    "options": [
      "certificate of urgency/need",
      "the tax collection agency",
      "free sector",
      "to divorce (your husband or wife)"
    ],
    "answer": "the tax collection agency"
  },
  {
    "question": "het beltegoed",
    "options": [
      "call credit",
      "to replace",
      "rubbish",
      "battery"
    ],
    "answer": "call credit"
  },
  {
    "question": "bestellen",
    "options": [
      "customer, client",
      "to order",
      "district",
      "amount"
    ],
    "answer": "to order"
  },
  {
    "question": "de bon",
    "options": [
      "possible",
      "coupon; receipt",
      "water rates/charges",
      "private individual"
    ],
    "answer": "coupon; receipt"
  },
  {
    "question": "de brand",
    "options": [
      "permission",
      "electricity/gas/utility/power company",
      "fire",
      "private individual"
    ],
    "answer": "fire"
  },
  {
    "question": "de brommer",
    "options": [
      "to separate waste",
      "annual bill",
      "moped",
      "in total"
    ],
    "answer": "moped"
  },
  {
    "question": "het chemisch afval",
    "options": [
      "chemical waste",
      "home insurance",
      "water rates/charges",
      "in total"
    ],
    "answer": "chemical waste"
  },
  {
    "question": "de container",
    "options": [
      "insurance",
      "skip, dumpster",
      "private individual",
      "moped"
    ],
    "answer": "skip, dumpster"
  },
  {
    "question": "het contract",
    "options": [
      "municipality, city, local council",
      "lessor, landlord",
      "possible",
      "contract"
    ],
    "answer": "contract"
  },
  {
    "question": "direct",
    "options": [
      "lease",
      "health insurance",
      "lessor, landlord",
      "directly"
    ],
    "answer": "directly"
  },
  {
    "question": "doorgeven",
    "options": [
      "the electric utility",
      "to inform",
      "(insurance) policy",
      "plastic"
    ],
    "answer": "to inform"
  },
  {
    "question": "de eengezinswoning",
    "options": [
      "chemical waste",
      "space, room",
      "single-family dwelling",
      "to divorce (your husband or wife)"
    ],
    "answer": "single-family dwelling"
  },
  {
    "question": "de elektricien",
    "options": [
      "building",
      "skip, dumpster",
      "electrician",
      "washing machine"
    ],
    "answer": "electrician"
  },
  {
    "question": "de elektriciteit",
    "options": [
      "tap",
      "exemption, being let off having to pay",
      "interest",
      "electricity"
    ],
    "answer": "electricity"
  },
  {
    "question": "de elektriciteitsmeter",
    "options": [
      "income",
      "vehicle insurance",
      "to repair, to fix",
      "electricity meter"
    ],
    "answer": "electricity meter"
  },
  {
    "question": "de elektriciteitsvoorziening",
    "options": [
      "the electric utility",
      "town hall",
      "careful, economical",
      "municipality, city, local council"
    ],
    "answer": "the electric utility"
  },
  {
    "question": "de energie",
    "options": [
      "energy",
      "battery",
      "instalment (amount)",
      "in total"
    ],
    "answer": "energy"
  },
  {
    "question": "het energiebedrijf",
    "options": [
      "electricity/gas/utility/power company",
      "garden",
      "notary",
      "to enrol"
    ],
    "answer": "electricity/gas/utility/power company"
  },
  {
    "question": "de energierekening",
    "options": [
      "phone bill",
      "to smell",
      "electricity/gas bill",
      "to request, to apply for"
    ],
    "answer": "electricity/gas bill"
  },
  {
    "question": "de etage",
    "options": [
      "storey, floor",
      "lift, elevator",
      "electricity",
      "house, home"
    ],
    "answer": "storey, floor"
  },
  {
    "question": "het gas",
    "options": [
      "electricity meter",
      "glass recycling bin",
      "gas",
      "income"
    ],
    "answer": "gas"
  },
  {
    "question": "de gasmeter",
    "options": [
      "gas meter",
      "area, region",
      "tax(es)",
      "housing association"
    ],
    "answer": "gas meter"
  },
  {
    "question": "het gebouw",
    "options": [
      "glass recycling bin",
      "insurance company",
      "to notify (the police/insurance agency)",
      "building"
    ],
    "answer": "building"
  },
  {
    "question": "gelijk hebben",
    "options": [
      "to be right",
      "electricity",
      "contract",
      "housing association"
    ],
    "answer": "to be right"
  },
  {
    "question": "de gemeente",
    "options": [
      "health insurance",
      "insurance",
      "the electric utility",
      "municipality, city, local council"
    ],
    "answer": "municipality, city, local council"
  },
  {
    "question": "het gemeentehuis",
    "options": [
      "rent",
      "to be right",
      "town hall",
      "public house"
    ],
    "answer": "town hall"
  },
  {
    "question": "geschikt",
    "options": [
      "energy",
      "inclusive, including",
      "by accident, accidentally",
      "suitable"
    ],
    "answer": "suitable"
  },
  {
    "question": "de gezondheid",
    "options": [
      "ball",
      "to enrol",
      "health",
      "bill"
    ],
    "answer": "health"
  },
  {
    "question": "de glasbak",
    "options": [
      "area, region",
      "glass recycling bin",
      "to paint",
      "dependent"
    ],
    "answer": "glass recycling bin"
  },
  {
    "question": "de huisvestingsvergunning",
    "options": [
      "to inform",
      "housing permit",
      "gas",
      "satisfied"
    ],
    "answer": "housing permit"
  },
  {
    "question": "huren",
    "options": [
      "air",
      "to rent",
      "repair(s)",
      "plumber, pipe fitter"
    ],
    "answer": "to rent"
  },
  {
    "question": "de huur",
    "options": [
      "to sign",
      "environment",
      "rent",
      "tap"
    ],
    "answer": "rent"
  },
  {
    "question": "de huurcommissie",
    "options": [
      "person seeking housing",
      "safe",
      "garden",
      "rent commission"
    ],
    "answer": "rent commission"
  },
  {
    "question": "het huurcontract",
    "options": [
      "the liability insurance for private persons",
      "health insurance",
      "lease",
      "person seeking housing"
    ],
    "answer": "lease"
  },
  {
    "question": "de huurtoeslag",
    "options": [
      "free sector",
      "inclusive, including",
      "to respond",
      "rent subsidy/benefit"
    ],
    "answer": "rent subsidy/benefit"
  },
  {
    "question": "de hypotheek",
    "options": [
      "mortgage",
      "skip, dumpster",
      "inclusive, including",
      "(classified) advertisement"
    ],
    "answer": "mortgage"
  },
  {
    "question": "de inboedel",
    "options": [
      "directly",
      "home contents",
      "building",
      "public house"
    ],
    "answer": "home contents"
  },
  {
    "question": "de inboedelverzekering",
    "options": [
      "electricity/gas bill",
      "(home) contents insurance",
      "customer, client",
      "to replace"
    ],
    "answer": "(home) contents insurance"
  },
  {
    "question": "inclusief",
    "options": [
      "the liability insurance for private persons",
      "inclusive, including",
      "to rent",
      "interest"
    ],
    "answer": "inclusive, including"
  },
  {
    "question": "het inkomen",
    "options": [
      "by accident, accidentally",
      "income",
      "rent",
      "premium, contribution"
    ],
    "answer": "income"
  },
  {
    "question": "inschrijven",
    "options": [
      "to enrol",
      "fixed number",
      "accommodation, somewhere to live",
      "interest"
    ],
    "answer": "to enrol"
  },
  {
    "question": "de jaarrekening",
    "options": [
      "annual bill",
      "bag",
      "coupon; receipt",
      "directly"
    ],
    "answer": "annual bill"
  },
  {
    "question": "de kabelaansluiting",
    "options": [
      "air",
      "cable connection",
      "washing machine",
      "contract"
    ],
    "answer": "cable connection"
  },
  {
    "question": "de keuken",
    "options": [
      "webcam",
      "to move house",
      "glass recycling bin",
      "kitchen"
    ],
    "answer": "kitchen"
  },
  {
    "question": "de klant",
    "options": [
      "public house",
      "health insurance",
      "fine",
      "customer, client"
    ],
    "answer": "customer, client"
  },
  {
    "question": "de kraan",
    "options": [
      "tap",
      "to divorce (your husband or wife)",
      "fine",
      "permit, license"
    ],
    "answer": "tap"
  },
  {
    "question": "de kwijtschelding",
    "options": [
      "the tax collection agency",
      "registration number",
      "exemption, being let off having to pay",
      "battery"
    ],
    "answer": "exemption, being let off having to pay"
  },
  {
    "question": "de lift",
    "options": [
      "fine",
      "lift, elevator",
      "water rates/charges",
      "permanent job"
    ],
    "answer": "lift, elevator"
  },
  {
    "question": "de loodgieter",
    "options": [
      "garden waste",
      "plumber, pipe fitter",
      "basic healthcare insurance",
      "rent subsidy/benefit"
    ],
    "answer": "plumber, pipe fitter"
  },
  {
    "question": "de lucht",
    "options": [
      "meter reading",
      "air",
      "ball",
      "rent"
    ],
    "answer": "air"
  },
  {
    "question": "de makelaar",
    "options": [
      "(electrical) appliance",
      "washing machine",
      "real estate agent",
      "apartment"
    ],
    "answer": "real estate agent"
  },
  {
    "question": "melden",
    "options": [
      "student",
      "to notify (the police/insurance agency)",
      "government benefit/payment",
      "nursing home"
    ],
    "answer": "to notify (the police/insurance agency)"
  },
  {
    "question": "de meterstand",
    "options": [
      "to sign",
      "meter reading",
      "in total",
      "health"
    ],
    "answer": "meter reading"
  },
  {
    "question": "het milieu",
    "options": [
      "compulsory, obligatory",
      "rubbish",
      "environment",
      "to disconnect, to cut off"
    ],
    "answer": "environment"
  },
  {
    "question": "mogelijk",
    "options": [
      "skip, dumpster",
      "phone bill",
      "(insurance) policy",
      "possible"
    ],
    "answer": "possible"
  },
  {
    "question": "netjes",
    "options": [
      "safe",
      "neat",
      "by accident, accidentally",
      "to disconnect, to cut off"
    ],
    "answer": "neat"
  },
  {
    "question": "de notaris",
    "options": [
      "notary",
      "directly",
      "electricity",
      "smoke"
    ],
    "answer": "notary"
  },
  {
    "question": "het onderhoud",
    "options": [
      "dependent",
      "maintenance",
      "municipality, city, local council",
      "to repair, to fix"
    ],
    "answer": "maintenance"
  },
  {
    "question": "per ongeluk",
    "options": [
      "insurance company",
      "water supply company",
      "damage",
      "by accident, accidentally"
    ],
    "answer": "by accident, accidentally"
  },
  {
    "question": "officieel",
    "options": [
      "building",
      "official",
      "by accident, accidentally",
      "vehicle insurance"
    ],
    "answer": "official"
  },
  {
    "question": "de opstalverzekering",
    "options": [
      "water supply company",
      "house insurance",
      "battery",
      "housing permit"
    ],
    "answer": "house insurance"
  },
  {
    "question": "de organisatie",
    "options": [
      "organization",
      "home contents",
      "(home) contents insurance",
      "exemption, being let off having to pay"
    ],
    "answer": "organization"
  },
  {
    "question": "de OZB (onroerendezaakbelasting)",
    "options": [
      "(home) contents insurance",
      "nursing home",
      "property tax/rates",
      "permanent job"
    ],
    "answer": "property tax/rates"
  },
  {
    "question": "de particulier",
    "options": [
      "safe",
      "private individual",
      "kitchen",
      "bag"
    ],
    "answer": "private individual"
  },
  {
    "question": "plastic",
    "options": [
      "meter reading",
      "permission",
      "phone bill",
      "plastic"
    ],
    "answer": "plastic"
  },
  {
    "question": "de polis",
    "options": [
      "to divorce (your husband or wife)",
      "(insurance) policy",
      "house, home",
      "to offer"
    ],
    "answer": "(insurance) policy"
  },
  {
    "question": "de premie",
    "options": [
      "premium, contribution",
      "notification of change of address",
      "repair(s)",
      "to request, to apply for"
    ],
    "answer": "premium, contribution"
  },
  {
    "question": "de provider",
    "options": [
      "to smell",
      "to rent",
      "provider",
      "electricity meter"
    ],
    "answer": "provider"
  },
  {
    "question": "reageren",
    "options": [
      "storey, floor",
      "exemption, being let off having to pay",
      "tax(es)",
      "to respond"
    ],
    "answer": "to respond"
  },
  {
    "question": "de regio",
    "options": [
      "rent commission",
      "gas meter",
      "area, region",
      "insurance"
    ],
    "answer": "area, region"
  },
  {
    "question": "het registratienummer",
    "options": [
      "registration number",
      "district",
      "the detached house",
      "by accident, accidentally"
    ],
    "answer": "registration number"
  },
  {
    "question": "de rekening",
    "options": [
      "breakdown, failure",
      "single-family dwelling",
      "official",
      "bill"
    ],
    "answer": "bill"
  },
  {
    "question": "de rente",
    "options": [
      "cable connection",
      "rubbish disposal charge",
      "district",
      "interest"
    ],
    "answer": "interest"
  },
  {
    "question": "de reparatie",
    "options": [
      "notification of change of address",
      "repair(s)",
      "to divorce (your husband or wife)",
      "insurance"
    ],
    "answer": "repair(s)"
  },
  {
    "question": "repareren",
    "options": [
      "permit, license",
      "maintenance",
      "to repair, to fix",
      "repair(s)"
    ],
    "answer": "to repair, to fix"
  },
  {
    "question": "de rioolheffing",
    "options": [
      "person seeking housing",
      "water rates/charges",
      "housing corporation",
      "district"
    ],
    "answer": "water rates/charges"
  },
  {
    "question": "de rook",
    "options": [
      "(personal) liability insurance/third-party insurance",
      "call credit",
      "to respond",
      "smoke"
    ],
    "answer": "smoke"
  },
  {
    "question": "de rotzooi",
    "options": [
      "energy",
      "the liability insurance for private persons",
      "rubbish",
      "fixed number"
    ],
    "answer": "rubbish"
  },
  {
    "question": "ruiken",
    "options": [
      "to smell",
      "to move house",
      "town hall",
      "insurance company"
    ],
    "answer": "to smell"
  },
  {
    "question": "de ruimte",
    "options": [
      "smoke",
      "website",
      "space, room",
      "gas"
    ],
    "answer": "space, room"
  },
  {
    "question": "de ruit",
    "options": [
      "rent commission",
      "alter, renovate",
      "window pane",
      "neat"
    ],
    "answer": "window pane"
  },
  {
    "question": "de schade",
    "options": [
      "to repair, to fix",
      "housing permit",
      "gas",
      "damage"
    ],
    "answer": "damage"
  },
  {
    "question": "scheiden",
    "options": [
      "to divorce (your husband or wife)",
      "basic healthcare insurance",
      "notary",
      "to disconnect, to cut off"
    ],
    "answer": "to divorce (your husband or wife)"
  },
  {
    "question": "schilderen",
    "options": [
      "suitable",
      "electricity/gas bill",
      "to paint",
      "webcam"
    ],
    "answer": "to paint"
  },
  {
    "question": "de servicekosten",
    "options": [
      "service costs/charges",
      "alter, renovate",
      "careful, economical",
      "suitable"
    ],
    "answer": "service costs/charges"
  },
  {
    "question": "de socialehuurwoning",
    "options": [
      "public house",
      "government benefit/payment",
      "tax(es)",
      "heating"
    ],
    "answer": "public house"
  },
  {
    "question": "de storing",
    "options": [
      "maintenance",
      "tap",
      "environment",
      "breakdown, failure"
    ],
    "answer": "breakdown, failure"
  },
  {
    "question": "de storm",
    "options": [
      "phone bill",
      "storm",
      "mortgage",
      "to inform"
    ],
    "answer": "storm"
  },
  {
    "question": "de student",
    "options": [
      "to inform",
      "to divorce (your husband or wife)",
      "kitchen",
      "student"
    ],
    "answer": "student"
  },
  {
    "question": "tekenen (contract)",
    "options": [
      "alter, renovate",
      "to order",
      "to sign",
      "storey, floor"
    ],
    "answer": "to sign"
  },
  {
    "question": "de telefoonrekening",
    "options": [
      "chemical waste",
      "phone bill",
      "insurance company",
      "cable connection"
    ],
    "answer": "phone bill"
  },
  {
    "question": "het termijnbedrag",
    "options": [
      "instalment (amount)",
      "the tax collection agency",
      "accommodation, somewhere to live",
      "bag"
    ],
    "answer": "instalment (amount)"
  },
  {
    "question": "tevreden",
    "options": [
      "rubbish",
      "environment",
      "satisfied",
      "basic healthcare insurance"
    ],
    "answer": "satisfied"
  },
  {
    "question": "toestemming",
    "options": [
      "premium, contribution",
      "permission",
      "to order",
      "housing permit"
    ],
    "answer": "permission"
  },
  {
    "question": "totaal",
    "options": [
      "home contents",
      "free sector",
      "in total",
      "property tax/rates"
    ],
    "answer": "in total"
  },
  {
    "question": "de tuin",
    "options": [
      "damage",
      "housing corporation",
      "garden",
      "the detached house"
    ],
    "answer": "garden"
  },
  {
    "question": "het tuinafval",
    "options": [
      "rubbish, trash, garbage",
      "garden waste",
      "(insurance) policy",
      "person seeking housing"
    ],
    "answer": "garden waste"
  },
  {
    "question": "de uitkering",
    "options": [
      "private individual",
      "rubbish disposal charge",
      "government benefit/payment",
      "A label"
    ],
    "answer": "government benefit/payment"
  },
  {
    "question": "de urgentieverklaring",
    "options": [
      "to offer",
      "certificate of urgency/need",
      "fixed number",
      "to rent"
    ],
    "answer": "certificate of urgency/need"
  },
  {
    "question": "de vaste baan",
    "options": [
      "permanent job",
      "the tax collection agency",
      "certificate of urgency/need",
      "rent subsidy/benefit"
    ],
    "answer": "permanent job"
  },
  {
    "question": "het vaste nummer",
    "options": [
      "vehicle insurance",
      "fixed number",
      "plumber, pipe fitter",
      "to replace"
    ],
    "answer": "fixed number"
  },
  {
    "question": "veilig",
    "options": [
      "registration number",
      "water rates/charges",
      "safe",
      "bag"
    ],
    "answer": "safe"
  },
  {
    "question": "verbouwen",
    "options": [
      "washing machine",
      "health insurance",
      "alter, renovate",
      "insurance"
    ],
    "answer": "alter, renovate"
  },
  {
    "question": "verhuizen",
    "options": [
      "bag",
      "notification of change of address",
      "to order",
      "water rates/charges"
    ],
    "answer": "notification of change of address"
  },
  {
    "question": "het verhuisbericht",
    "options": [
      "accommodation, somewhere to live",
      "to move house",
      "coupon; receipt",
      "fixed number"
    ],
    "answer": "to move house"
  },
  {
    "question": "de vergunning",
    "options": [
      "firm, concern, company",
      "official",
      "electricity meter",
      "permit, license"
    ],
    "answer": "permit, license"
  },
  {
    "question": "de verhuurder",
    "options": [
      "firm, concern, company",
      "phone bill",
      "lessor, landlord",
      "washing machine"
    ],
    "answer": "lessor, landlord"
  },
  {
    "question": "de verkoper",
    "options": [
      "building",
      "certificate of urgency/need",
      "(personal) liability insurance/third-party insurance",
      "seller, selling party"
    ],
    "answer": "seller, selling party"
  },
  {
    "question": "verplicht",
    "options": [
      "satisfied",
      "compulsory, obligatory",
      "glass recycling bin",
      "customer, client"
    ],
    "answer": "compulsory, obligatory"
  },
  {
    "question": "vervangen",
    "options": [
      "electrician",
      "rent commission",
      "to replace",
      "washing machine"
    ],
    "answer": "to replace"
  },
  {
    "question": "de verwarming",
    "options": [
      "real estate agent",
      "heating",
      "building",
      "to take care, make sure (that)"
    ],
    "answer": "heating"
  },
  {
    "question": "de verzekering",
    "options": [
      "home insurance",
      "environment",
      "insurance",
      "electricity meter"
    ],
    "answer": "insurance"
  },
  {
    "question": "de verzekeringsmaatschappij",
    "options": [
      "skip, dumpster",
      "instalment (amount)",
      "website",
      "insurance company"
    ],
    "answer": "insurance company"
  },
  {
    "question": "het verzorgingshuis",
    "options": [
      "nursing home",
      "chemical waste",
      "to take care, make sure (that)",
      "insurance company"
    ],
    "answer": "nursing home"
  },
  {
    "question": "het vrijstaand huis",
    "options": [
      "fixed number",
      "the detached house",
      "water supply company",
      "neat"
    ],
    "answer": "the detached house"
  },
  {
    "question": "de vrije sector",
    "options": [
      "rent",
      "free sector",
      "customer, client",
      "accommodation, somewhere to live"
    ],
    "answer": "free sector"
  },
  {
    "question": "de WA-verzekering",
    "options": [
      "ball",
      "vehicle insurance",
      "to sign",
      "exemption, being let off having to pay"
    ],
    "answer": "vehicle insurance"
  },
  {
    "question": "de wasmachine",
    "options": [
      "washing machine",
      "to request, to apply for",
      "to separate waste",
      "(insurance) policy"
    ],
    "answer": "washing machine"
  },
  {
    "question": "het waterbedrijf",
    "options": [
      "to separate waste",
      "fixed number",
      "rubbish",
      "water supply company"
    ],
    "answer": "water supply company"
  },
  {
    "question": "de webcam",
    "options": [
      "public house",
      "plumber, pipe fitter",
      "real estate agent",
      "webcam"
    ],
    "answer": "webcam"
  },
  {
    "question": "de website",
    "options": [
      "website",
      "the detached house",
      "bill",
      "chemical waste"
    ],
    "answer": "website"
  },
  {
    "question": "de wijk",
    "options": [
      "suitable",
      "air",
      "district",
      "health"
    ],
    "answer": "district"
  },
  {
    "question": "de woning",
    "options": [
      "house, home",
      "satisfied",
      "registration number",
      "to sign"
    ],
    "answer": "house, home"
  },
  {
    "question": "de woningbouwvereniging",
    "options": [
      "housing association",
      "nursing home",
      "apartment",
      "A label"
    ],
    "answer": "housing association"
  },
  {
    "question": "de woningcorporatie",
    "options": [
      "electricity/gas/utility/power company",
      "housing corporation",
      "exemption, being let off having to pay",
      "in total"
    ],
    "answer": "housing corporation"
  },
  {
    "question": "de woningzoekende",
    "options": [
      "satisfied",
      "notification of change of address",
      "person seeking housing",
      "(classified) advertisement"
    ],
    "answer": "person seeking housing"
  },
  {
    "question": "de woonhuisverzekering",
    "options": [
      "battery",
      "electricity",
      "inclusive, including",
      "home insurance"
    ],
    "answer": "home insurance"
  },
  {
    "question": "de woonruimte",
    "options": [
      "vehicle insurance",
      "area, region",
      "(electrical) appliance",
      "accommodation, somewhere to live"
    ],
    "answer": "accommodation, somewhere to live"
  },
  {
    "question": "de zak",
    "options": [
      "skip, dumpster",
      "electricity meter",
      "bag",
      "gas meter"
    ],
    "answer": "bag"
  },
  {
    "question": "zorgen (voor/dat)",
    "options": [
      "damage",
      "building",
      "to take care, make sure (that)",
      "skip, dumpster"
    ],
    "answer": "to take care, make sure (that)"
  },
  {
    "question": "de zorgverzekering",
    "options": [
      "housing permit",
      "registration number",
      "to sign",
      "health insurance"
    ],
    "answer": "health insurance"
  },
  {
    "question": "zuinig",
    "options": [
      "careful, economical",
      "firm, concern, company",
      "insurance company",
      "heating"
    ],
    "answer": "careful, economical"
  },
  {
    "question": "aanmelden",
    "options": [
      "fire brigade",
      "to register",
      "subscription",
      "health"
    ],
    "answer": "to register"
  },
  {
    "question": "de aanvullende verzekering",
    "options": [
      "patient registration card/tag",
      "additional insurance",
      "prescription",
      "illness, disease"
    ],
    "answer": "additional insurance"
  },
  {
    "question": "het abonnement",
    "options": [
      "to be careful, watch out",
      "to keep, store",
      "box",
      "subscription"
    ],
    "answer": "subscription"
  },
  {
    "question": "de afdeling",
    "options": [
      "prescription",
      "fish",
      "department",
      "toothache"
    ],
    "answer": "department"
  },
  {
    "question": "de aids",
    "options": [
      "cd",
      "AIDS",
      "additional insurance",
      "compulsory"
    ],
    "answer": "AIDS"
  },
  {
    "question": "het alarmnummer",
    "options": [
      "emergency number",
      "medicine",
      "doctor",
      "back"
    ],
    "answer": "emergency number"
  },
  {
    "question": "de ambulance",
    "options": [
      "fire brigade",
      "phone subscription",
      "basic (compulsory) insurance",
      "ambulance"
    ],
    "answer": "ambulance"
  },
  {
    "question": "de apotheek",
    "options": [
      "back",
      "pharmacy",
      "AIDS",
      "doctor"
    ],
    "answer": "pharmacy"
  },
  {
    "question": "de arts",
    "options": [
      "interpreter",
      "additional insurance",
      "doctor",
      "accident"
    ],
    "answer": "doctor"
  },
  {
    "question": "de assistente",
    "options": [
      "to spoil, go bad",
      "assistant",
      "online",
      "condom"
    ],
    "answer": "assistant"
  },
  {
    "question": "de automaat",
    "options": [
      "automat, dispenser",
      "fatal, it kills",
      "fish",
      "phone subscription"
    ],
    "answer": "automat, dispenser"
  },
  {
    "question": "de avonddienst",
    "options": [
      "beer",
      "on average",
      "to organise",
      "evening shift/duty"
    ],
    "answer": "evening shift/duty"
  },
  {
    "question": "de balie",
    "options": [
      "(well) cooked",
      "health insurance",
      "club",
      "desk"
    ],
    "answer": "desk"
  },
  {
    "question": "de basisverzekering",
    "options": [
      "locum doctor, doctor on call",
      "STD, sexually transmitted disease",
      "basic (compulsory) insurance",
      "ailment, symptom"
    ],
    "answer": "basic (compulsory) insurance"
  },
  {
    "question": "bederven",
    "options": [
      "cancer",
      "satisfied",
      "whole-wheat bread",
      "to spoil, go bad"
    ],
    "answer": "to spoil, go bad"
  },
  {
    "question": "de behandeling",
    "options": [
      "nutrition",
      "to spell",
      "treatment",
      "deductible"
    ],
    "answer": "treatment"
  },
  {
    "question": "de belasting",
    "options": [
      "paracetamol",
      "tax",
      "box",
      "automat, dispenser"
    ],
    "answer": "tax"
  },
  {
    "question": "de Belastingdienst",
    "options": [
      "club, association, society",
      "plastic",
      "night shift/duty, graveyard shift",
      "the tax collection agency"
    ],
    "answer": "the tax collection agency"
  },
  {
    "question": "het bestuur",
    "options": [
      "(executive) committee",
      "library",
      "subscription",
      "referral (letter)"
    ],
    "answer": "(executive) committee"
  },
  {
    "question": "bewaren",
    "options": [
      "to have a picnic",
      "automat, dispenser",
      "to keep, store",
      "(well) cooked"
    ],
    "answer": "to keep, store"
  },
  {
    "question": "bewegen",
    "options": [
      "to move",
      "unhealthy, not good for you",
      "bill",
      "paracetamol"
    ],
    "answer": "to move"
  },
  {
    "question": "de bibliotheek",
    "options": [
      "library",
      "lung cancer",
      "night shift/duty, graveyard shift",
      "fish"
    ],
    "answer": "library"
  },
  {
    "question": "het bier",
    "options": [
      "AIDS",
      "specialist",
      "beer",
      "fatal, it kills"
    ],
    "answer": "beer"
  },
  {
    "question": "de bijdrage",
    "options": [
      "community centre",
      "patient registration card/tag",
      "contribution",
      "premium, contribution"
    ],
    "answer": "contribution"
  },
  {
    "question": "de bijsluiter",
    "options": [
      "STD, sexually transmitted disease",
      "addicted",
      "instruction pamphlet",
      "lung"
    ],
    "answer": "instruction pamphlet"
  },
  {
    "question": "de bloeddruk",
    "options": [
      "additional insurance",
      "packaging, box",
      "meal",
      "blood pressure"
    ],
    "answer": "blood pressure"
  },
  {
    "question": "de brandweer",
    "options": [
      "to introduce yourself, to meet (for the first time)",
      "accident",
      "fire brigade",
      "risk (at your own risk), excess"
    ],
    "answer": "fire brigade"
  },
  {
    "question": "breken (gebroken)",
    "options": [
      "identity card",
      "night shift/duty, graveyard shift",
      "sleeping pill",
      "to break"
    ],
    "answer": "to break"
  },
  {
    "question": "het buurthuis",
    "options": [
      "community centre",
      "physiotherapist",
      "to have a picnic",
      "blood pressure"
    ],
    "answer": "community centre"
  },
  {
    "question": "de cd",
    "options": [
      "cd",
      "to move house",
      "ambulance",
      "medicine"
    ],
    "answer": "cd"
  },
  {
    "question": "de club",
    "options": [
      "club",
      "AIDS",
      "health insurer",
      "beach"
    ],
    "answer": "club"
  },
  {
    "question": "het condoom",
    "options": [
      "condom",
      "heart",
      "cd",
      "pharmacy"
    ],
    "answer": "condom"
  },
  {
    "question": "declareren",
    "options": [
      "pay attention to",
      "to declare, to claim",
      "condom",
      "satisfied"
    ],
    "answer": "to declare, to claim"
  },
  {
    "question": "de dienst",
    "options": [
      "health care",
      "to move house",
      "pharmacy",
      "(work) shift"
    ],
    "answer": "(work) shift"
  },
  {
    "question": "de dierentuin",
    "options": [
      "zoo",
      "illness, disease",
      "to declare, to claim",
      "contribution"
    ],
    "answer": "zoo"
  },
  {
    "question": "dodelijk",
    "options": [
      "pill",
      "fatal, it kills",
      "specialist",
      "lung"
    ],
    "answer": "fatal, it kills"
  },
  {
    "question": "doorverwijzen",
    "options": [
      "pill",
      "health care allowance",
      "to refer",
      "to go for a walk"
    ],
    "answer": "to refer"
  },
  {
    "question": "het doosje",
    "options": [
      "basic (compulsory) insurance",
      "box",
      "museum",
      "addicted"
    ],
    "answer": "box"
  },
  {
    "question": "de drogist",
    "options": [
      "assistant",
      "drugstore, chemist’s",
      "evening shift/duty",
      "toothache"
    ],
    "answer": "drugstore, chemist’s"
  },
  {
    "question": "eigen bijdrage",
    "options": [
      "copayment",
      "bottle",
      "health costs/expenses",
      "beach"
    ],
    "answer": "copayment"
  },
  {
    "question": "eigen risico",
    "options": [
      "to earn",
      "gynaecologist",
      "deductible",
      "fire brigade"
    ],
    "answer": "deductible"
  },
  {
    "question": "het etiket",
    "options": [
      "pay attention to",
      "molar",
      "label, sticker",
      "trouble with, pain"
    ],
    "answer": "label, sticker"
  },
  {
    "question": "het flesje",
    "options": [
      "ambulance",
      "trouble with, pain",
      "bottle",
      "subscription"
    ],
    "answer": "bottle"
  },
  {
    "question": "de fysiotherapeut",
    "options": [
      "beer",
      "treatment",
      "health care allowance",
      "physiotherapist"
    ],
    "answer": "physiotherapist"
  },
  {
    "question": "gaar",
    "options": [
      "(well) cooked",
      "satisfied",
      "to introduce yourself, to meet (for the first time)",
      "desk"
    ],
    "answer": "(well) cooked"
  },
  {
    "question": "het gaatje",
    "options": [
      "hole, cavity",
      "sleeping pill",
      "additional insurance",
      "health costs/expenses"
    ],
    "answer": "hole, cavity"
  },
  {
    "question": "de geboortedatum",
    "options": [
      "plastic",
      "condom",
      "operation",
      "date of birth"
    ],
    "answer": "date of birth"
  },
  {
    "question": "gemiddeld",
    "options": [
      "whole-wheat bread",
      "cigarette",
      "wine",
      "on average"
    ],
    "answer": "on average"
  },
  {
    "question": "de gezondheid",
    "options": [
      "to have breakfast",
      "patient registration card/tag",
      "health",
      "museum"
    ],
    "answer": "health"
  },
  {
    "question": "de gezondheidszorg",
    "options": [
      "evening shift/duty",
      "identity card",
      "health care",
      "sleeping pill"
    ],
    "answer": "health care"
  },
  {
    "question": "de gynaecoloog",
    "options": [
      "on its own accord",
      "cd",
      "phone",
      "gynaecologist"
    ],
    "answer": "gynaecologist"
  },
  {
    "question": "het hart",
    "options": [
      "health",
      "to meet",
      "doctor",
      "heart"
    ],
    "answer": "heart"
  },
  {
    "question": "de huisarts",
    "options": [
      "family doctor, GP",
      "physiotherapist",
      "the tax collection agency",
      "body"
    ],
    "answer": "family doctor, GP"
  },
  {
    "question": "de huisartsenpost",
    "options": [
      "to break",
      "prescription",
      "evening shift/duty",
      "locum doctor, doctor on call"
    ],
    "answer": "locum doctor, doctor on call"
  },
  {
    "question": "het identiteitsbewijs",
    "options": [
      "to break",
      "online",
      "identity card",
      "health insurer"
    ],
    "answer": "identity card"
  },
  {
    "question": "inschrijven",
    "options": [
      "to enrol",
      "box",
      "prescription",
      "dental insurance"
    ],
    "answer": "to enrol"
  },
  {
    "question": "de kanker",
    "options": [
      "evening shift/duty",
      "wine",
      "cancer",
      "pharmacy"
    ],
    "answer": "cancer"
  },
  {
    "question": "de kans",
    "options": [
      "packaging, box",
      "accident",
      "fish",
      "chance, risk"
    ],
    "answer": "chance, risk"
  },
  {
    "question": "kennismaken",
    "options": [
      "pill",
      "to introduce yourself, to meet (for the first time)",
      "safe",
      "lung"
    ],
    "answer": "to introduce yourself, to meet (for the first time)"
  },
  {
    "question": "de kies",
    "options": [
      "copayment",
      "to take care (of/that)",
      "molar",
      "basic (compulsory) insurance"
    ],
    "answer": "molar"
  },
  {
    "question": "de kiespijn",
    "options": [
      "safe",
      "toothache",
      "to spoil, go bad",
      "copayment"
    ],
    "answer": "toothache"
  },
  {
    "question": "de klacht",
    "options": [
      "examination",
      "(health) insurance papers",
      "to have breakfast",
      "ailment, symptom"
    ],
    "answer": "ailment, symptom"
  },
  {
    "question": "de koelkast",
    "options": [
      "trouble with, pain",
      "physiotherapist",
      "refrigerator",
      "cancer"
    ],
    "answer": "refrigerator"
  },
  {
    "question": "de koorts",
    "options": [
      "contribution",
      "to declare, to claim",
      "fever, temperature",
      "insurance"
    ],
    "answer": "fever, temperature"
  },
  {
    "question": "last van",
    "options": [
      "zoo",
      "trouble with, pain",
      "identity card",
      "safe"
    ],
    "answer": "trouble with, pain"
  },
  {
    "question": "letten op",
    "options": [
      "AIDS",
      "to keep, store",
      "to refer",
      "pay attention to"
    ],
    "answer": "pay attention to"
  },
  {
    "question": "het lichaam",
    "options": [
      "compulsory",
      "packet",
      "body",
      "sleeping pill"
    ],
    "answer": "body"
  },
  {
    "question": "het lid",
    "options": [
      "member",
      "STD, sexually transmitted disease",
      "to eat sweets/candy",
      "on average"
    ],
    "answer": "member"
  },
  {
    "question": "de long",
    "options": [
      "copayment",
      "lung",
      "(executive) committee",
      "(health) insurance papers"
    ],
    "answer": "lung"
  },
  {
    "question": "de longkanker",
    "options": [
      "pill",
      "stairs",
      "plastic",
      "lung cancer"
    ],
    "answer": "lung cancer"
  },
  {
    "question": "de maaltijd",
    "options": [
      "treatment",
      "meal",
      "label, sticker",
      "eye specialist"
    ],
    "answer": "meal"
  },
  {
    "question": "het medicijn",
    "options": [
      "website",
      "by telephone",
      "medicine",
      "ambulance"
    ],
    "answer": "medicine"
  },
  {
    "question": "melden",
    "options": [
      "doctor",
      "(executive) committee",
      "to notify (the police/insurance agency)",
      "health care allowance"
    ],
    "answer": "to notify (the police/insurance agency)"
  },
  {
    "question": "het museum",
    "options": [
      "hole, cavity",
      "library",
      "physiotherapist",
      "museum"
    ],
    "answer": "museum"
  },
  {
    "question": "de nachtdienst",
    "options": [
      "night shift/duty, graveyard shift",
      "library",
      "deductible",
      "fire brigade"
    ],
    "answer": "night shift/duty, graveyard shift"
  },
  {
    "question": "het onderzoek",
    "options": [
      "to swallow, to take",
      "bill",
      "subscription",
      "examination"
    ],
    "answer": "examination"
  },
  {
    "question": "het ongelukje",
    "options": [
      "wine",
      "family doctor, GP",
      "accident",
      "identity card"
    ],
    "answer": "accident"
  },
  {
    "question": "ongezond",
    "options": [
      "unhealthy, not good for you",
      "outpatients’ clinic",
      "gynaecologist",
      "automat, dispenser"
    ],
    "answer": "unhealthy, not good for you"
  },
  {
    "question": "online",
    "options": [
      "label, sticker",
      "department",
      "online",
      "to swallow, to take"
    ],
    "answer": "online"
  },
  {
    "question": "het ontbijt",
    "options": [
      "gynaecologist",
      "hole, cavity",
      "insurance",
      "breakfast"
    ],
    "answer": "breakfast"
  },
  {
    "question": "ontbijten",
    "options": [
      "to have breakfast",
      "insurance",
      "(health) insurance papers",
      "(well) cooked"
    ],
    "answer": "to have breakfast"
  },
  {
    "question": "ontmoeten",
    "options": [
      "to meet",
      "chance, risk",
      "risk (at your own risk), excess",
      "health insurance"
    ],
    "answer": "to meet"
  },
  {
    "question": "de oogarts",
    "options": [
      "health",
      "finger",
      "eye specialist",
      "health insurance"
    ],
    "answer": "eye specialist"
  },
  {
    "question": "de operatie",
    "options": [
      "hole, cavity",
      "STD, sexually transmitted disease",
      "operation",
      "family doctor, GP"
    ],
    "answer": "operation"
  },
  {
    "question": "de opname",
    "options": [
      "instruction pamphlet",
      "packet",
      "(hospital) admission, hospitalization",
      "waiting list"
    ],
    "answer": "(hospital) admission, hospitalization"
  },
  {
    "question": "oppassen (voor iets)",
    "options": [
      "department",
      "to organise",
      "to be careful, watch out",
      "satisfied"
    ],
    "answer": "to be careful, watch out"
  },
  {
    "question": "organiseren",
    "options": [
      "interpreter",
      "to organise",
      "to have breakfast",
      "examination"
    ],
    "answer": "to organise"
  },
  {
    "question": "het pakje",
    "options": [
      "premium, contribution",
      "zoo",
      "packet",
      "amusement park"
    ],
    "answer": "packet"
  },
  {
    "question": "de paracetamol",
    "options": [
      "on its own accord",
      "paracetamol",
      "family doctor, GP",
      "by telephone"
    ],
    "answer": "paracetamol"
  },
  {
    "question": "de patiëntenpas",
    "options": [
      "to have breakfast",
      "patient registration card/tag",
      "label, sticker",
      "cancer"
    ],
    "answer": "patient registration card/tag"
  },
  {
    "question": "picknicken",
    "options": [
      "health",
      "to earn",
      "sugar",
      "to have a picnic"
    ],
    "answer": "to have a picnic"
  },
  {
    "question": "de pil",
    "options": [
      "heart",
      "drugstore, chemist’s",
      "additional insurance",
      "pill"
    ],
    "answer": "pill"
  },
  {
    "question": "plastic",
    "options": [
      "cancer",
      "zoo",
      "bill",
      "plastic"
    ],
    "answer": "plastic"
  },
  {
    "question": "de polikliniek",
    "options": [
      "paracetamol",
      "outpatients’ clinic",
      "bottle",
      "compulsory"
    ],
    "answer": "outpatients’ clinic"
  },
  {
    "question": "de premie",
    "options": [
      "interpreter",
      "premium, contribution",
      "instruction pamphlet",
      "contribution"
    ],
    "answer": "premium, contribution"
  },
  {
    "question": "het pretpark",
    "options": [
      "amusement park",
      "basic (compulsory) insurance",
      "operation",
      "to have a picnic"
    ],
    "answer": "amusement park"
  },
  {
    "question": "de proefles",
    "options": [
      "trial lesson",
      "illness, disease",
      "to move house",
      "on its own accord"
    ],
    "answer": "trial lesson"
  },
  {
    "question": "het recept",
    "options": [
      "hole, cavity",
      "prescription",
      "to eat sweets/candy",
      "dental insurance"
    ],
    "answer": "prescription"
  },
  {
    "question": "de rekening",
    "options": [
      "lung",
      "referral (letter)",
      "pay attention to",
      "bill"
    ],
    "answer": "bill"
  },
  {
    "question": "het restaurant",
    "options": [
      "restaurant",
      "health insurance",
      "to have a picnic",
      "locum doctor, doctor on call"
    ],
    "answer": "restaurant"
  },
  {
    "question": "het risico (eigen risico)",
    "options": [
      "beach",
      "to earn",
      "on average",
      "risk (at your own risk), excess"
    ],
    "answer": "risk (at your own risk), excess"
  },
  {
    "question": "de rug",
    "options": [
      "beach",
      "family doctor, GP",
      "back",
      "department"
    ],
    "answer": "back"
  },
  {
    "question": "de schade",
    "options": [
      "damage",
      "examination",
      "to organise",
      "sex"
    ],
    "answer": "damage"
  },
  {
    "question": "schilderen",
    "options": [
      "heart",
      "on its own accord",
      "to paint",
      "assistant"
    ],
    "answer": "to paint"
  },
  {
    "question": "de seks",
    "options": [
      "(hospital) admission, hospitalization",
      "sex",
      "health insurer",
      "to take care (of/that)"
    ],
    "answer": "sex"
  },
  {
    "question": "de sigaret",
    "options": [
      "tax",
      "cigarette",
      "packet",
      "date of birth"
    ],
    "answer": "cigarette"
  },
  {
    "question": "het slaaptablet",
    "options": [
      "night shift/duty, graveyard shift",
      "to refer",
      "sleeping pill",
      "restaurant"
    ],
    "answer": "sleeping pill"
  },
  {
    "question": "slikken",
    "options": [
      "to break",
      "fatal, it kills",
      "to swallow, to take",
      "breakfast"
    ],
    "answer": "to swallow, to take"
  },
  {
    "question": "snoepen",
    "options": [
      "to eat sweets/candy",
      "heart",
      "basic (compulsory) insurance",
      "toothache"
    ],
    "answer": "to eat sweets/candy"
  },
  {
    "question": "de soa",
    "options": [
      "STD, sexually transmitted disease",
      "refrigerator",
      "to earn",
      "body"
    ],
    "answer": "STD, sexually transmitted disease"
  },
  {
    "question": "de specialist",
    "options": [
      "specialist",
      "blood pressure",
      "to move house",
      "patient registration card/tag"
    ],
    "answer": "specialist"
  },
  {
    "question": "spellen",
    "options": [
      "to enrol",
      "plastic",
      "to spell",
      "on its own accord"
    ],
    "answer": "to spell"
  },
  {
    "question": "de spoedeisende hulp",
    "options": [
      "community centre",
      "label, sticker",
      "emergency assistance",
      "body"
    ],
    "answer": "emergency assistance"
  },
  {
    "question": "het strand",
    "options": [
      "stairs",
      "desk",
      "club",
      "beach"
    ],
    "answer": "beach"
  },
  {
    "question": "de suiker",
    "options": [
      "drugstore, chemist’s",
      "sugar",
      "community centre",
      "the tax collection agency"
    ],
    "answer": "sugar"
  },
  {
    "question": "de tandarts",
    "options": [
      "fat",
      "fire brigade",
      "library",
      "dentist"
    ],
    "answer": "dentist"
  },
  {
    "question": "de tandartsverzekering",
    "options": [
      "desk",
      "blood pressure",
      "dental insurance",
      "bottle"
    ],
    "answer": "dental insurance"
  },
  {
    "question": "de telefoon",
    "options": [
      "phone",
      "risk (at your own risk), excess",
      "hole, cavity",
      "to enrol"
    ],
    "answer": "phone"
  },
  {
    "question": "het telefoonabonnement",
    "options": [
      "to break",
      "safe",
      "desk",
      "phone subscription"
    ],
    "answer": "phone subscription"
  },
  {
    "question": "telefonisch",
    "options": [
      "by telephone",
      "safe",
      "back",
      "addicted"
    ],
    "answer": "by telephone"
  },
  {
    "question": "tevreden",
    "options": [
      "(health) insurance papers",
      "satisfied",
      "plastic",
      "desk"
    ],
    "answer": "satisfied"
  },
  {
    "question": "de tolk",
    "options": [
      "to have breakfast",
      "interpreter",
      "museum",
      "packaging, box"
    ],
    "answer": "interpreter"
  },
  {
    "question": "het tolkencentrum",
    "options": [
      "interpreting service",
      "condom",
      "STD, sexually transmitted disease",
      "to spoil, go bad"
    ],
    "answer": "interpreting service"
  },
  {
    "question": "de trap",
    "options": [
      "website",
      "dental insurance",
      "stairs",
      "eye specialist"
    ],
    "answer": "stairs"
  },
  {
    "question": "vanzelf",
    "options": [
      "paracetamol",
      "restaurant",
      "refrigerator",
      "on its own accord"
    ],
    "answer": "on its own accord"
  },
  {
    "question": "veilig",
    "options": [
      "safe",
      "lung cancer",
      "beer",
      "(health) insurance papers"
    ],
    "answer": "safe"
  },
  {
    "question": "verdienen",
    "options": [
      "accident",
      "library",
      "to earn",
      "interpreter"
    ],
    "answer": "to earn"
  },
  {
    "question": "vereniging",
    "options": [
      "restaurant",
      "club, association, society",
      "to move house",
      "molar"
    ],
    "answer": "club, association, society"
  },
  {
    "question": "verhuizen",
    "options": [
      "risk (at your own risk), excess",
      "safe",
      "to move house",
      "cd"
    ],
    "answer": "to move house"
  },
  {
    "question": "de verpakking",
    "options": [
      "packaging, box",
      "(well) cooked",
      "library",
      "bill"
    ],
    "answer": "packaging, box"
  },
  {
    "question": "verplicht",
    "options": [
      "STD, sexually transmitted disease",
      "compulsory",
      "dental insurance",
      "pregnant"
    ],
    "answer": "compulsory"
  },
  {
    "question": "verslaafd",
    "options": [
      "gynaecologist",
      "refrigerator",
      "addicted",
      "to have breakfast"
    ],
    "answer": "addicted"
  },
  {
    "question": "de verwijsbrief",
    "options": [
      "to move",
      "cd",
      "referral (letter)",
      "to spoil, go bad"
    ],
    "answer": "referral (letter)"
  },
  {
    "question": "de verzekering",
    "options": [
      "insurance",
      "physiotherapist",
      "automat, dispenser",
      "doctor"
    ],
    "answer": "insurance"
  },
  {
    "question": "het verzekeringsbewijs",
    "options": [
      "(health) insurance papers",
      "locum doctor, doctor on call",
      "to have breakfast",
      "club"
    ],
    "answer": "(health) insurance papers"
  },
  {
    "question": "vet",
    "options": [
      "fat",
      "cd",
      "to introduce yourself, to meet (for the first time)",
      "community centre"
    ],
    "answer": "fat"
  },
  {
    "question": "de vinger",
    "options": [
      "night shift/duty, graveyard shift",
      "finger",
      "meal",
      "interpreting service"
    ],
    "answer": "finger"
  },
  {
    "question": "de vis",
    "options": [
      "fish",
      "pill",
      "to eat sweets/candy",
      "library"
    ],
    "answer": "fish"
  },
  {
    "question": "de voeding",
    "options": [
      "to spell",
      "emergency assistance",
      "fat",
      "nutrition"
    ],
    "answer": "nutrition"
  },
  {
    "question": "het volkorenbrood",
    "options": [
      "whole-wheat bread",
      "date of birth",
      "trouble with, pain",
      "automat, dispenser"
    ],
    "answer": "whole-wheat bread"
  },
  {
    "question": "de wachtlijst",
    "options": [
      "waiting list",
      "copayment",
      "breakfast",
      "to introduce yourself, to meet (for the first time)"
    ],
    "answer": "waiting list"
  },
  {
    "question": "wandelen",
    "options": [
      "molar",
      "to spell",
      "health insurer",
      "to go for a walk"
    ],
    "answer": "to go for a walk"
  },
  {
    "question": "de website",
    "options": [
      "to meet",
      "stairs",
      "interpreter",
      "website"
    ],
    "answer": "website"
  },
  {
    "question": "de weekenddienst",
    "options": [
      "referral (letter)",
      "eye specialist",
      "weekend shift/duty",
      "to earn"
    ],
    "answer": "weekend shift/duty"
  },
  {
    "question": "de wijn",
    "options": [
      "to meet",
      "wine",
      "sleeping pill",
      "packet"
    ],
    "answer": "wine"
  },
  {
    "question": "de ziekte",
    "options": [
      "interpreter",
      "locum doctor, doctor on call",
      "illness, disease",
      "trouble with, pain"
    ],
    "answer": "illness, disease"
  },
  {
    "question": "de ziektekosten",
    "options": [
      "health costs/expenses",
      "operation",
      "pharmacy",
      "restaurant"
    ],
    "answer": "health costs/expenses"
  },
  {
    "question": "zorgen (voor/dat)",
    "options": [
      "to take care (of/that)",
      "compulsory",
      "by telephone",
      "beach"
    ],
    "answer": "to take care (of/that)"
  },
  {
    "question": "de zorgtoeslag",
    "options": [
      "automat, dispenser",
      "health care allowance",
      "to go for a walk",
      "basic (compulsory) insurance"
    ],
    "answer": "health care allowance"
  },
  {
    "question": "de zorgverzekeraar",
    "options": [
      "ambulance",
      "health insurer",
      "AIDS",
      "to move house"
    ],
    "answer": "health insurer"
  },
  {
    "question": "de zorgverzekering",
    "options": [
      "AIDS",
      "lung",
      "health insurance",
      "cigarette"
    ],
    "answer": "health insurance"
  },
  {
    "question": "zwanger",
    "options": [
      "pregnant",
      "heart",
      "sugar",
      "health costs/expenses"
    ],
    "answer": "pregnant"
  },
  {
    "question": "de berg",
    "options": [
      "mountain",
      "province",
      "cool",
      "leaf (leaves)"
    ],
    "answer": "mountain"
  },
  {
    "question": "beschermen",
    "options": [
      "to protect",
      "umbrella",
      "dunes",
      "democracy"
    ],
    "answer": "to protect"
  },
  {
    "question": "bewolkt",
    "options": [
      "refugee",
      "plan",
      "to freeze",
      "cloudy"
    ],
    "answer": "cloudy"
  },
  {
    "question": "het blad (bladeren)",
    "options": [
      "entrance",
      "princess",
      "leaf (leaves)",
      "to travel"
    ],
    "answer": "leaf (leaves)"
  },
  {
    "question": "het buurland",
    "options": [
      "point",
      "nature",
      "mountain",
      "neighbouring country"
    ],
    "answer": "neighbouring country"
  },
  {
    "question": "de democratie",
    "options": [
      "government",
      "to vote",
      "democracy",
      "nature"
    ],
    "answer": "democracy"
  },
  {
    "question": "dichtbevolkt",
    "options": [
      "densely populated",
      "point",
      "tower",
      "territory"
    ],
    "answer": "densely populated"
  },
  {
    "question": "de dijk",
    "options": [
      "dyke",
      "prince",
      "lake",
      "island"
    ],
    "answer": "dyke"
  },
  {
    "question": "de duinen",
    "options": [
      "sea level",
      "religion",
      "princess",
      "dunes"
    ],
    "answer": "dunes"
  },
  {
    "question": "het eiland",
    "options": [
      "government",
      "to vote",
      "to freeze",
      "island"
    ],
    "answer": "island"
  },
  {
    "question": "de file",
    "options": [
      "plan",
      "changeable",
      "traffic jam",
      "parliament"
    ],
    "answer": "traffic jam"
  },
  {
    "question": "de gastarbeider",
    "options": [
      "changeable",
      "president",
      "cloudy",
      "guest worker"
    ],
    "answer": "guest worker"
  },
  {
    "question": "het gebied",
    "options": [
      "to freeze",
      "entrance",
      "territory",
      "river"
    ],
    "answer": "territory"
  },
  {
    "question": "het geloof",
    "options": [
      "prince",
      "changeable",
      "religion",
      "to protect"
    ],
    "answer": "religion"
  },
  {
    "question": "geloven",
    "options": [
      "to believe",
      "season",
      "harbour",
      "dyke"
    ],
    "answer": "to believe"
  },
  {
    "question": "de haven",
    "options": [
      "harbour",
      "to protect",
      "president",
      "traffic jam"
    ],
    "answer": "harbour"
  },
  {
    "question": "de herfst",
    "options": [
      "autumn",
      "tower",
      "polder",
      "changeable"
    ],
    "answer": "autumn"
  },
  {
    "question": "de hoofdstad",
    "options": [
      "densely populated",
      "capital city",
      "province",
      "point"
    ],
    "answer": "capital city"
  },
  {
    "question": "de ingang",
    "options": [
      "entrance",
      "sea level",
      "leaf (leaves)",
      "changeable"
    ],
    "answer": "entrance"
  },
  {
    "question": "koel",
    "options": [
      "cool",
      "prince",
      "square kilometre",
      "to vote"
    ],
    "answer": "cool"
  },
  {
    "question": "de lente",
    "options": [
      "spring",
      "government",
      "princess",
      "dunes"
    ],
    "answer": "spring"
  },
  {
    "question": "het meer",
    "options": [
      "island",
      "entrance",
      "capital city",
      "lake"
    ],
    "answer": "lake"
  },
  {
    "question": "de minister",
    "options": [
      "square kilometre",
      "umbrella",
      "the Minister",
      "airport"
    ],
    "answer": "the Minister"
  },
  {
    "question": "de nationaliteit",
    "options": [
      "nationality",
      "cloudy",
      "square kilometre",
      "prince"
    ],
    "answer": "nationality"
  },
  {
    "question": "de natuur",
    "options": [
      "nature",
      "guest worker",
      "tower",
      "prince"
    ],
    "answer": "nature"
  },
  {
    "question": "de paraplu",
    "options": [
      "umbrella",
      "territory",
      "to skate",
      "island"
    ],
    "answer": "umbrella"
  },
  {
    "question": "het parlement",
    "options": [
      "umbrella",
      "parliament",
      "to protect",
      "island"
    ],
    "answer": "parliament"
  },
  {
    "question": "het plan",
    "options": [
      "province",
      "guest worker",
      "season",
      "plan"
    ],
    "answer": "plan"
  },
  {
    "question": "de polder",
    "options": [
      "island",
      "government",
      "polder",
      "province"
    ],
    "answer": "polder"
  },
  {
    "question": "de president",
    "options": [
      "to vote",
      "entrance",
      "parliament",
      "president"
    ],
    "answer": "president"
  },
  {
    "question": "de prins",
    "options": [
      "guest worker",
      "religion",
      "prince",
      "island"
    ],
    "answer": "prince"
  },
  {
    "question": "de prinses",
    "options": [
      "leaf (leaves)",
      "cloudy",
      "princess",
      "cool"
    ],
    "answer": "princess"
  },
  {
    "question": "de provincie",
    "options": [
      "province",
      "nationality",
      "spring",
      "religion"
    ],
    "answer": "province"
  },
  {
    "question": "het punt",
    "options": [
      "river",
      "residence permit",
      "nature",
      "point"
    ],
    "answer": "point"
  },
  {
    "question": "de regering",
    "options": [
      "traffic jam",
      "government",
      "to travel",
      "airport"
    ],
    "answer": "government"
  },
  {
    "question": "reizen",
    "options": [
      "airport",
      "to travel",
      "refugee",
      "leaf (leaves)"
    ],
    "answer": "to travel"
  },
  {
    "question": "de rivier",
    "options": [
      "season",
      "government",
      "harbour",
      "river"
    ],
    "answer": "river"
  },
  {
    "question": "schaatsen",
    "options": [
      "to skate",
      "tower",
      "to freeze",
      "autumn"
    ],
    "answer": "to skate"
  },
  {
    "question": "schijnen",
    "options": [
      "dyke",
      "dunes",
      "refugee",
      "to shine"
    ],
    "answer": "to shine"
  },
  {
    "question": "het seizoen",
    "options": [
      "season",
      "airport",
      "to vote",
      "the Minister"
    ],
    "answer": "season"
  },
  {
    "question": "de snelweg",
    "options": [
      "autumn",
      "lake",
      "freeway, highway",
      "territory"
    ],
    "answer": "freeway, highway"
  },
  {
    "question": "stemmen",
    "options": [
      "harbour",
      "to vote",
      "neighbouring country",
      "sea level"
    ],
    "answer": "to vote"
  },
  {
    "question": "de toren",
    "options": [
      "tower",
      "harbour",
      "to vote",
      "airport"
    ],
    "answer": "tower"
  },
  {
    "question": "de verblijfsvergunning",
    "options": [
      "to protect",
      "residence permit",
      "lake",
      "government"
    ],
    "answer": "residence permit"
  },
  {
    "question": "de vierkante kilometer",
    "options": [
      "to protect",
      "to vote",
      "square kilometre",
      "leaf (leaves)"
    ],
    "answer": "square kilometre"
  },
  {
    "question": "het vliegveld",
    "options": [
      "refugee",
      "province",
      "airport",
      "religion"
    ],
    "answer": "airport"
  },
  {
    "question": "de vluchteling",
    "options": [
      "cool",
      "refugee",
      "changeable",
      "government"
    ],
    "answer": "refugee"
  },
  {
    "question": "vriezen",
    "options": [
      "cool",
      "harbour",
      "to travel",
      "to freeze"
    ],
    "answer": "to freeze"
  },
  {
    "question": "wisselvallig",
    "options": [
      "changeable",
      "autumn",
      "tower",
      "princess"
    ],
    "answer": "changeable"
  },
  {
    "question": "de zeespiegel",
    "options": [
      "to protect",
      "dunes",
      "sea level",
      "polder"
    ],
    "answer": "sea level"
  },
  {
    "question": "aankijken",
    "options": [
      "to look at",
      "suit",
      "suffers from",
      "to stink"
    ],
    "answer": "to look at"
  },
  {
    "question": "aanraken",
    "options": [
      "to touch",
      "to stink",
      "to greet",
      "to thank"
    ],
    "answer": "to touch"
  },
  {
    "question": "agenda de",
    "options": [
      "to congratulate",
      "spring",
      "agenda",
      "to rest"
    ],
    "answer": "agenda"
  },
  {
    "question": "bedanken",
    "options": [
      "to thank",
      "gift",
      "egg",
      "plant"
    ],
    "answer": "to thank"
  },
  {
    "question": "begrafenis de",
    "options": [
      "funeral",
      "wedding",
      "fireworks",
      "to get acquainted"
    ],
    "answer": "funeral"
  },
  {
    "question": "beschuit met muisjes",
    "options": [
      "invitation",
      "snack",
      "biscuit with sprinkles",
      "check-out"
    ],
    "answer": "biscuit with sprinkles"
  },
  {
    "question": "beterschap",
    "options": [
      "get well soon",
      "dress",
      "congratulations",
      "to succeed / pass"
    ],
    "answer": "get well soon"
  },
  {
    "question": "beurt de",
    "options": [
      "biscuit with sprinkles",
      "transport ticket",
      "to take a number",
      "turn"
    ],
    "answer": "turn"
  },
  {
    "question": "bruiloft de",
    "options": [
      "funeral",
      "sky / heaven",
      "wedding",
      "to treat (with food)"
    ],
    "answer": "wedding"
  },
  {
    "question": "cadeau het",
    "options": [
      "dress",
      "gift",
      "to stink",
      "check-in"
    ],
    "answer": "gift"
  },
  {
    "question": "cadeaubon de",
    "options": [
      "gift card",
      "kiss",
      "reception",
      "friendly"
    ],
    "answer": "gift card"
  },
  {
    "question": "collega de",
    "options": [
      "sky / heaven",
      "colleague",
      "silence compartment",
      "spring"
    ],
    "answer": "colleague"
  },
  {
    "question": "crematie de",
    "options": [
      "get well soon",
      "to kiss",
      "directly",
      "cremation"
    ],
    "answer": "cremation"
  },
  {
    "question": "cultuur de",
    "options": [
      "culture",
      "mess",
      "kiss",
      "to treat (with food)"
    ],
    "answer": "culture"
  },
  {
    "question": "dansen",
    "options": [
      "turn",
      "to dance",
      "to stink",
      "passed / succeeded"
    ],
    "answer": "to dance"
  },
  {
    "question": "diploma het",
    "options": [
      "diploma",
      "invitation",
      "to be ashamed",
      "suit"
    ],
    "answer": "diploma"
  },
  {
    "question": "direct",
    "options": [
      "to invite",
      "directly",
      "candy",
      "agenda"
    ],
    "answer": "directly"
  },
  {
    "question": "dode de",
    "options": [
      "the deceased",
      "snack",
      "condolences",
      "cake"
    ],
    "answer": "the deceased"
  },
  {
    "question": "ei het",
    "options": [
      "to succeed / pass",
      "kiss",
      "shoe",
      "egg"
    ],
    "answer": "egg"
  },
  {
    "question": "feliciteren",
    "options": [
      "to celebrate",
      "to decorate",
      "transport ticket",
      "to congratulate"
    ],
    "answer": "to congratulate"
  },
  {
    "question": "formeel",
    "options": [
      "turn",
      "formal",
      "congratulations",
      "passed / succeeded"
    ],
    "answer": "formal"
  },
  {
    "question": "gecondoleerd",
    "options": [
      "faith",
      "to touch",
      "gift card",
      "condolences"
    ],
    "answer": "condolences"
  },
  {
    "question": "gefeliciteerd",
    "options": [
      "public transport",
      "congratulations",
      "friendly",
      "directly"
    ],
    "answer": "congratulations"
  },
  {
    "question": "gek",
    "options": [
      "gift card",
      "dress",
      "to touch",
      "crazy / strange"
    ],
    "answer": "crazy / strange"
  },
  {
    "question": "geloof het",
    "options": [
      "knowledge / acquaintance",
      "faith",
      "get well soon",
      "gift"
    ],
    "answer": "faith"
  },
  {
    "question": "gemeentehuis het",
    "options": [
      "town hall",
      "to play soccer",
      "candy",
      "fireworks"
    ],
    "answer": "town hall"
  },
  {
    "question": "geslaagd",
    "options": [
      "passed / succeeded",
      "to succeed / pass",
      "formal",
      "egg"
    ],
    "answer": "passed / succeeded"
  },
  {
    "question": "gesprek(je) het",
    "options": [
      "to greet",
      "conversation",
      "to congratulate",
      "to celebrate"
    ],
    "answer": "conversation"
  },
  {
    "question": "gewoonte de",
    "options": [
      "snack",
      "flag",
      "habit / custom",
      "little game"
    ],
    "answer": "habit / custom"
  },
  {
    "question": "groeten",
    "options": [
      "education / training",
      "kiss",
      "to greet",
      "colleague"
    ],
    "answer": "to greet"
  },
  {
    "question": "hapje het",
    "options": [
      "to treat (with food)",
      "faith",
      "mess",
      "snack"
    ],
    "answer": "snack"
  },
  {
    "question": "hemel de",
    "options": [
      "ID card",
      "gift card",
      "flag",
      "sky / heaven"
    ],
    "answer": "sky / heaven"
  },
  {
    "question": "identiteitsbewijs het",
    "options": [
      "little game",
      "ID card",
      "passed / succeeded",
      "kiss"
    ],
    "answer": "ID card"
  },
  {
    "question": "inchecken",
    "options": [
      "crazy / strange",
      "flag",
      "friendly",
      "check-in"
    ],
    "answer": "check-in"
  },
  {
    "question": "in elk geval",
    "options": [
      "to look after",
      "invitation",
      "mess",
      "in any case"
    ],
    "answer": "in any case"
  },
  {
    "question": "informeel",
    "options": [
      "public transport card",
      "informal",
      "fare dodging",
      "condolences"
    ],
    "answer": "informal"
  },
  {
    "question": "jurk de",
    "options": [
      "friendly",
      "to play soccer",
      "check-out",
      "dress"
    ],
    "answer": "dress"
  },
  {
    "question": "kaarsje het",
    "options": [
      "to thank",
      "candle",
      "town hall",
      "reception"
    ],
    "answer": "candle"
  },
  {
    "question": "kennis de",
    "options": [
      "to treat (with food)",
      "to notice",
      "waiting room",
      "knowledge / acquaintance"
    ],
    "answer": "knowledge / acquaintance"
  },
  {
    "question": "kennismaken",
    "options": [
      "diploma",
      "in any case",
      "suit",
      "to get acquainted"
    ],
    "answer": "to get acquainted"
  },
  {
    "question": "kerstboom de",
    "options": [
      "Christmas tree",
      "to fast",
      "friendly",
      "to treat (with food)"
    ],
    "answer": "Christmas tree"
  },
  {
    "question": "koekje het",
    "options": [
      "agenda",
      "informal",
      "cookie",
      "to look after"
    ],
    "answer": "cookie"
  },
  {
    "question": "kostuum het",
    "options": [
      "to greet",
      "good luck / strength",
      "habit / custom",
      "suit"
    ],
    "answer": "suit"
  },
  {
    "question": "last van",
    "options": [
      "knowledge / acquaintance",
      "suffers from",
      "to look after",
      "culture"
    ],
    "answer": "suffers from"
  },
  {
    "question": "lente de",
    "options": [
      "to greet",
      "spring",
      "get well soon",
      "to invite"
    ],
    "answer": "spring"
  },
  {
    "question": "liedje het",
    "options": [
      "to look after",
      "to notice",
      "transport ticket",
      "song"
    ],
    "answer": "song"
  },
  {
    "question": "liefde de",
    "options": [
      "love",
      "to get acquainted",
      "agenda",
      "candy"
    ],
    "answer": "love"
  },
  {
    "question": "merken",
    "options": [
      "dress",
      "to notice",
      "crazy / strange",
      "fare dodging"
    ],
    "answer": "to notice"
  },
  {
    "question": "een nummertje trekken",
    "options": [
      "to treat (with food)",
      "to take a number",
      "fireworks",
      "public transport"
    ],
    "answer": "to take a number"
  },
  {
    "question": "officieel",
    "options": [
      "queue / line",
      "in any case",
      "official",
      "job interview"
    ],
    "answer": "official"
  },
  {
    "question": "openbaar vervoer het",
    "options": [
      "kiss",
      "egg",
      "public transport",
      "to notice"
    ],
    "answer": "public transport"
  },
  {
    "question": "opleiding de",
    "options": [
      "education / training",
      "to play soccer",
      "to treat (with food)",
      "birthday"
    ],
    "answer": "education / training"
  },
  {
    "question": "oranje",
    "options": [
      "orange",
      "to kiss",
      "to stink",
      "to celebrate"
    ],
    "answer": "orange"
  },
  {
    "question": "ov-chipkaart de",
    "options": [
      "mess",
      "the deceased",
      "turn",
      "public transport card"
    ],
    "answer": "public transport card"
  },
  {
    "question": "oppassen op",
    "options": [
      "to look after",
      "to stink",
      "reception",
      "check-in"
    ],
    "answer": "to look after"
  },
  {
    "question": "plant de",
    "options": [
      "plant",
      "to be ashamed",
      "to rest",
      "gift"
    ],
    "answer": "plant"
  },
  {
    "question": "receptie de",
    "options": [
      "reception",
      "informal",
      "silence compartment",
      "to notice"
    ],
    "answer": "reception"
  },
  {
    "question": "rij de",
    "options": [
      "to play soccer",
      "queue / line",
      "culture",
      "hall / venue"
    ],
    "answer": "queue / line"
  },
  {
    "question": "roepen",
    "options": [
      "culture",
      "faith",
      "to call",
      "snack"
    ],
    "answer": "to call"
  },
  {
    "question": "rommel de",
    "options": [
      "to stink",
      "mess",
      "cookie",
      "good luck / strength"
    ],
    "answer": "mess"
  },
  {
    "question": "rusten",
    "options": [
      "egg",
      "to rest",
      "to thank",
      "job interview"
    ],
    "answer": "to rest"
  },
  {
    "question": "zich schamen",
    "options": [
      "to be ashamed",
      "invitation",
      "to thank",
      "to take a number"
    ],
    "answer": "to be ashamed"
  },
  {
    "question": "schoen de",
    "options": [
      "to look after",
      "garbage",
      "shoe",
      "hall / venue"
    ],
    "answer": "shoe"
  },
  {
    "question": "slagen",
    "options": [
      "cremation",
      "to succeed / pass",
      "friendly",
      "fireworks"
    ],
    "answer": "to succeed / pass"
  },
  {
    "question": "snoep het",
    "options": [
      "hall / venue",
      "check-out",
      "candy",
      "cremation"
    ],
    "answer": "candy"
  },
  {
    "question": "sollicitatiegesprek het",
    "options": [
      "birthday",
      "mandatory",
      "job interview",
      "faith"
    ],
    "answer": "job interview"
  },
  {
    "question": "spelletje het",
    "options": [
      "in any case",
      "little game",
      "candy",
      "silence compartment"
    ],
    "answer": "little game"
  },
  {
    "question": "sterkte",
    "options": [
      "to notice",
      "good luck / strength",
      "transport ticket",
      "cake"
    ],
    "answer": "good luck / strength"
  },
  {
    "question": "stiltecoupé de",
    "options": [
      "congratulations",
      "silence compartment",
      "to take a number",
      "to stink"
    ],
    "answer": "silence compartment"
  },
  {
    "question": "stinken",
    "options": [
      "shoe",
      "passed / succeeded",
      "check-in",
      "to stink"
    ],
    "answer": "to stink"
  },
  {
    "question": "taart de",
    "options": [
      "to succeed / pass",
      "cake",
      "diploma",
      "to take a number"
    ],
    "answer": "cake"
  },
  {
    "question": "tot ziens",
    "options": [
      "transport ticket",
      "to succeed / pass",
      "hall / venue",
      "goodbye"
    ],
    "answer": "goodbye"
  },
  {
    "question": "trakteren",
    "options": [
      "in love",
      "reception",
      "to treat (with food)",
      "get well soon"
    ],
    "answer": "to treat (with food)"
  },
  {
    "question": "uitchecken",
    "options": [
      "colleague",
      "condolences",
      "garbage",
      "check-out"
    ],
    "answer": "check-out"
  },
  {
    "question": "uitnodigen",
    "options": [
      "to invite",
      "plant",
      "the deceased",
      "little game"
    ],
    "answer": "to invite"
  },
  {
    "question": "uitnodiging de",
    "options": [
      "invitation",
      "to notice",
      "kiss",
      "snack"
    ],
    "answer": "invitation"
  },
  {
    "question": "vasten",
    "options": [
      "to fast",
      "to congratulate",
      "transport ticket",
      "to kiss"
    ],
    "answer": "to fast"
  },
  {
    "question": "verjaardag de",
    "options": [
      "to congratulate",
      "birthday",
      "cake",
      "good luck / strength"
    ],
    "answer": "birthday"
  },
  {
    "question": "verliefd",
    "options": [
      "in love",
      "informal",
      "mandatory",
      "public transport"
    ],
    "answer": "in love"
  },
  {
    "question": "verplicht",
    "options": [
      "fireworks",
      "knowledge / acquaintance",
      "to fast",
      "mandatory"
    ],
    "answer": "mandatory"
  },
  {
    "question": "versieren",
    "options": [
      "to decorate",
      "habit / custom",
      "crazy / strange",
      "cake"
    ],
    "answer": "to decorate"
  },
  {
    "question": "vervoersbewijs het",
    "options": [
      "to play soccer",
      "transport ticket",
      "gift card",
      "public transport card"
    ],
    "answer": "transport ticket"
  },
  {
    "question": "vieren",
    "options": [
      "condolences",
      "invitation",
      "friendly",
      "to celebrate"
    ],
    "answer": "to celebrate"
  },
  {
    "question": "vlag de",
    "options": [
      "in love",
      "flag",
      "crazy / strange",
      "knowledge / acquaintance"
    ],
    "answer": "flag"
  },
  {
    "question": "voetballen",
    "options": [
      "fare dodging",
      "fireworks",
      "to play soccer",
      "directly"
    ],
    "answer": "to play soccer"
  },
  {
    "question": "vriendelijk",
    "options": [
      "to fast",
      "friendly",
      "turn",
      "directly"
    ],
    "answer": "friendly"
  },
  {
    "question": "vuilnis de",
    "options": [
      "garbage",
      "gift",
      "funeral",
      "condolences"
    ],
    "answer": "garbage"
  },
  {
    "question": "vuurwerk het",
    "options": [
      "spring",
      "song",
      "fireworks",
      "colleague"
    ],
    "answer": "fireworks"
  },
  {
    "question": "wachtkamer de",
    "options": [
      "waiting room",
      "in any case",
      "colleague",
      "orange"
    ],
    "answer": "waiting room"
  },
  {
    "question": "wandelen",
    "options": [
      "suffers from",
      "to walk",
      "habit / custom",
      "knowledge / acquaintance"
    ],
    "answer": "to walk"
  },
  {
    "question": "zaal de",
    "options": [
      "reception",
      "to touch",
      "the deceased",
      "hall / venue"
    ],
    "answer": "hall / venue"
  },
  {
    "question": "zoen de",
    "options": [
      "kiss",
      "candle",
      "garbage",
      "congratulations"
    ],
    "answer": "kiss"
  },
  {
    "question": "zoenen",
    "options": [
      "to kiss",
      "mandatory",
      "to fast",
      "to treat (with food)"
    ],
    "answer": "to kiss"
  },
  {
    "question": "zwart reizen",
    "options": [
      "condolences",
      "fare dodging",
      "cookie",
      "to greet"
    ],
    "answer": "fare dodging"
  }
]